(Woman moaning)
(Sighs)
(Cup falls)
It is true what they say
about the northern girls.
(Giggles)
Did you hear the king's in Winterfell?
I did hear something about that.
And the queen and her twin brother.
They say that he is the most handsome man
in the Seven Kingdoms.
And the other brother?
- The queen has two brothers?
- There's the pretty one...
and there's the clever one.
Mmm...
I hear they call him the Imp.
I hear he hates that nickname.
Oh? I hear he's more than earned it.
I hear he's a drunken little lecher,
prone to all manner of perversions.
Clever girl.
We've been expecting you, Lord Tyrion.
Have you?
- Already?
- Oh!
- The gods gave me one blessing.
- (Laughs)
(Door opens)
- Don't get up.
- My lord.
Should I explain to you the meaning of
a closed door in a whorehouse, brother?
You have much to teach me, no doubt,
but our sister craves your attention.
She has odd cravings, our sister.
A family trait.