(Music playing)
(Watch ticking)
(Seagulls cawing)
(Bell ringing)
(Foghorn blows)
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
I'm a sitting duck out here.
So move then.
Come on.
Charlie.
Load it up.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on.
- Liquid gold, boyo.
- That's it.
(Music playing)
Come on, are we
fucking done here?
Boys, we're straight on to New York,
so anyone needs a piss,
you take it now.
No?
Then let's go.
Son of a bitch.
Hold up.
Slow down.
(Brakes squeal)
He's still breathing.
Fuck him.
Get him off the road.
- (Gun cocks)
- [Man]: Get 'em up!
Up!
Get your fucking hands in the air.
Drop the heaters.
- You stupid fuck.
- Drop it I said!
You too, fat boy.
Drop it!
Drop your weapon.
You know whose
fucking load this is?
It's pretty fucking
obvious now, ain't it?
[Woman]: "Coward, monster,
vicious brute,
friend to thief and prostitute,
conscience dulled by demon rum,
liquor, thy name's
delirium".
Tomorrow we awaken
to a new dawn.
And on the eve of this
momentous occasion,
it is my pleasure
to introduce...
Atlantic city's
esteemed treasurer,
the honorable enoch Thompson.
Mrs. McGarry, thank you
for that stirring poem.
Will you send me a copy?
[Woman]:
What a nice man.
Ladies.
Years ago there was a young boy
who lived in this very city.
The winter of '88,
some of you remember,
a blizzard
of biblical proportions.
The family was snowbound
and freezing,
without food or heat.
The father vanished...
laid to waste by
alcohol.
And so it was left
to this boy,
this little man of tender years
to fend for himself
and his family.
Off in the cold he went,
worn shoes wrapped in rags,
newspaper lining
his thin wool coat,
as he trudged
chest deep in snow
to the rail yard,
foraging on hands
and bloody knees
for scraps of coal,
hoping for some potatoes
spilled from a ruptured sack.
Finding none,
he took a broom handle...
and in desperation,
killed his family's dinner:
Three wharf rats hiding in the
hold of a ship.
(Gasps)
Terrible, yes.
But the family survived.
And the little boy?
Well, the little boy
speaks to you tonight
- from this very podium.
- (Applause)
Prohibition means progress.
Never again will families
be robbed of their fathers,
held hostage by alcohol.
How proud I am...
to live in a nation which,
God willing, this year will finally
give s women the right to vote.
Ladies, I regret to inform you...
that I have been called away
on urgent county business...
and therefore will be unable
to stay for the potluck.
- (Groans)
- Shh-shh.
In closing, however,
let me say this:
Without the continued support
of good decent women...
like you, men like me...
would be nowhere.
Thank you and God bless.
In the trenches
once we ate dog meat.
But rats?
First rule of politics, kiddo:
Never let the truth get
in the way of a good story.
Barker: Come on in, boys!
Don't be shy.
Meet the gals who put
the "ooh" in ooh-la-la.
Step right up, friends.
Whatcha waiting for?
Lovely ladies
direct from Paris...
France.
- (Giggles)
- Young ladies,
I know there are attractions
that your parents
would like to take you to,
but this
is not one of them.
Ladies, take them away, yes.
- They should have been gone a
long time ago. - (Laughs)
Don't be afraid, fellas.
They won't bite...
unless you want them to.
- Hey, Nucky, how you doing?
- Not as good as you, Wendell.
- Good evening, Nucky.
- Hey, how are ya?
- How are you, Nucky?
- Nice to see you.
(Band playing)
[Man]:
Say it ain't so, Joe.
To the end of the world!
(Baby crying)
All right,
take it easy, fellas.
I got it!
I got it! Over here.
[Man]: Hey, you got some rye?
I want some gin... gin!
[Nucky]:
Thanks, ace.
- Is my brother here?
- Upstairs.
They all are.
(Laughing)
I wanted to arrest him, but he
had 24 hours left. I couldn't.
(Clinking glass)
Boys, boys, boys.
Mr. Mayor, friends,
fellow members
of the city council,
as you know,
in less than two hours
liquor will be declared
illegal by decree
of the distinguished gentlemen
of our nation's congress.
(Group moans)
To those beautiful,
ignorant bastards!
(Toasting)
Rest assured that dry
though the country may be,
I am in the midst
of concluding arrangements
that will keep Atlantic city
wet as a mermaid's twat.
Jeez, Nucky,
you're fucking mermaids now?
Every vote counts,
Mr. Mayor.
[Man]: A republican
through and through.
The opportunity that is the Volstead act
has not merely knocked, my friends,
- it has kicked our fucking doors in!
- (Agreeing)
- I'll believe it when I see it.
- Come on, George,
it'll be like prohibition
never happened,
but for one thing...
prices will increase twentyfold.
What kind of sucker will pay three
clams for a drink worth 15c?
- You.
- You'll pay 12 clams...
for a piece of cooze
that ain't worth nothing.
Yeah, you pay.
You pay.
I know.
Now he's...
he's on the trolley.
Number one...
we got a product...
- a fella's gotta have.
- Yeah.
Even better is that we got a
product he ain't allowed to have.
- They might as well outlaw smoking.
- [Mayor]: A man's on holiday,
believe me, he wants a drink,
he'll pay the price for it.
- That's right.
- How about the law?
The law?
I am the law, Georgie boy.
Or are you so fucking soused
you thought I'm Lillian Gish, huh?
I mean this ain't a flower.
It's not a flower.
I'm gonna kick him outta here right now.
You're outta here.
- The feds!
- You're under arrest.
The feds, the fucking prohis.
Oh, the feds,
the fucking pro...
dogcatchers with badges.
With all due deference
to dogcatchers.
Now, as ward bosses,
you'll each be responsible...
for taking orders
and collecting...
from your restaurants,
hotels, what have you.
Those orders will be reviewed
by my brother and his men,
who'll supervise delivery.
Which brings me
to a few personnel changes.
- You all remember Jimmy Darmody?
- Welcome back, kid!
- Welcome home, Jimmy.
- Welcome back, kid.
- Good to see you.
- Gave them huns hell, I heard.
- Sure did.
- [Nucky]: He did.
And now that he's made
the world safe for democracy,
he's back to lend us
a hand too.
In three weeks paddy Ryan
is taking over...
as chief clerk
of the fourth ward.
Jimmy here'll be
pat's man Friday.
- Attaboy.
- Paddy.
- Congratulations, paddy.
- Gentlemen, it's an honor.
- Paddy Ryan... a good man.
- Look out, Mayor,
the kid'll have
your job one day.
He can have it
right now if he wants it.
- Give it time, Mr. Mayor.
- Welcome aboard, paddy.
(Chatting)
10, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two,
one.
("Taps" playing)
Prohibition!
(Cheering)
(Growling)
Hey, where are you going?
- What's eating you?
- Nothing. I don't know.
- My stomach.
- Oh, go have a brioski.
- Will you look at this shit?
- James.
No, put it in your mouth.
Dempsey... "champ was
no draft dodger.
He explains his status
during war".
- So what did he say? - I dunno.
He supported his mother.
- It's a bunch of baloney.
- They couldn't write it if it wasn't true.
Wise up, Ange.
It's a bill of goods.
You think a fella would give
up that type of opportunity...
to go fight for his country?
What? Why are you looking
at me like that?
Princeton wasn't exactly the
heavyweight championship, Angela.
Have you given it
any more thought?
I'd be 25 by the time I graduated...
almost 26.
- I could go to work.
- Doing what?
- Painting pictures?
- (Boy babbles)
And what about skeezix here?
- Where are you going?
- Hey, sit down, eat your food.
No no, come on.
You gotta eat this mush.
Get up. Come on.
What about you, right?
- Yeah.
- Drink your milk.
One more bite.
You know, you could learn a lot
working for Ryan maybe.
- Are the eggs ready yet?
- Hold your horses!
Your mother's screwy if she thinks
I'm gonna work for a sap like Ryan.
- Ryan's a sap.
- Ryan is a sap.
Don't say that.
- I drank all my milk.
- Good.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna talk to Nucky.
I don't know, two years
killing Jerries
doesn't exactly prepare you
for a whole lot else.
(Gunshots)
[Man]:
As prohibition agents,
you represent the finest
America has to offer...
the first line of defense in
the war against illegal liquor,
stout-hearted men,
centurions for the modern age,
unswerving in duty
and incorruptible...
in character.
Raise your right hands.
- I...
- State your name...
- (Names)
- Do so solemnly swear...
To uphold the laws of the
constitution of the United States...
To root out criminality
in all forms...
To root out
criminality in all forms...
And vigorously uphold
all laws...
Nuck.
Nucky.
Oh.
What time is it?
2:30.
- Nucky, are you up?
- What the fuck's the matter?
There's a lady waiting to see you.
She's been waiting over an hour.
She says it is urgent.
She's pregnant.
- (Woman moans)
- What?
- You met her last night.
- Last night?
She saw you talk or something.
Ah ah!
The tempremence league.
(Sighs)
- (Groans)
- Why didn't you say so?
- I just did.
- "Pregnant woman here to see you"...
Give me a fucking nosebleed.
I... I... I...
I would never...
I am so sorry.
I would never inter...
- (door slams)
- Inter... interrupt.
I go. I...
Man: Gentlemen, welcome
to the Brighton.
We got a nice
high floor, right?
I want to look at the water.
Oh, rest assured, sir, all our
rooms have an ocean view.
- Boys.
- Mr. Torrio.
Rothstein.
See, I told you he'd come.
[Torrio]: Big Jim Colosimo,
Arnold Rothstein,
and Charlie Luciano.
Charlie, how are you?
(Speaking Italian)
How you doing?
Come on.
(Door opens)
You must please come this way.
David, I am so sorry I'm late.
Tell Nucky I ain't got all day.
(Clears throat)
Mrs. Schröder to see you.
Please, have a seat.
May I offer you tea?
- (Irish accent) Thank you, I'm fine.
- No, it's no trouble.
- Have you eaten?
- Thank you no.
I mean I have, yes.
I've eaten, but I...
Okay, relax.
Please.
- No more appointments.
- Ja.
Is that a bit of the old country
I hear in your voice?
My husband says I sound
like an immigrant.
Ah. But we're all
immigrants, are we not?
Tell me how I can help you.
First of all, sir,
I would never...
but when I heard
you speak, I...
There there now.
My apologies.
My husband,
he has a weakness
for the dice games.
He's a drinker as well
on occasion.
Is this your first child?
Our third.
We've a boy and a girl.
Do you have children
of your own, Mr. Thompson?
I'm sorry.
That was quite forward.
Not at all.
I do not.
I lost my wife to consumption.
Oh, I'm sorry.
She was very pretty.
She was.
Hey, uh, Nucky?
- I'm gonna go now.
- Oh, I'm in a meeting.
No, please, I...
No, Mrs. Schröder,
Lucy Danziger.
Hello.
Hi.
So am I gonna see ya later?
I'll get in touch.
- I'm sorry. I...
- No.
- I... she's my...
- It's...
Does your husband work?
He's a baker's helper.
But till tourist season
and with winter,
and the children
without boots, I...
Your story moved me so.
If you could see your way
to give him a job, sir?
As you say...
until tourist season.
However...
This should see you
through winter.
I'm not here
looking for charity.
I insist.
I don't know what to say,
how to thank you.
I'd be honored to name
my child after you.
Enoch?
You couldn't possibly
be so cruel.
Jimmy?
- See that Mrs. Schröder gets home.
- I'm fine to walk, please.
No no no, you are
in no condition.
- Thank you, Mr. Thompson.
- Sure.
Pardon me.
Your friends from Chicago checked in.
The New York gangs too.
- We're all set for tonight then?
- 8:00, the Traymore.
- Good.
- Say, Nuck,
I was hoping
to bend your ear...
Drop her off then meet me
at the pier later.
¶ The laddie told the girlie
he must go away ¶
¶ oh, and her little heart
with grief 'most broke ¶
¶ well, she said,
"you know I love you, honey ¶
¶ I love you, honey,
best of all ¶
¶ so, baby, don't go away" ¶
¶ just as he went to go ¶
¶ it grieved the girlie so ¶
¶ these words ¶
¶ he heard her say ¶
¶ some ¶
¶ of ¶
¶ these days ¶
¶ oh, you'll miss me, honey ¶
¶ some of these days ¶
¶ you're gonna feel so lonely ¶
¶ you're gonna miss
my hugging ¶
¶ you're gonna
miss my kissing ¶
¶ you're gonna miss me, honey ¶
¶ when I'm far away ¶
¶ I feel so lonely ¶
¶ just for you only ¶
¶ Mmm, you know, honey ¶
¶ I let you have your way ¶
¶ and when you leave me ¶
- ¶ I know it will grieve me...
¶ - (Horn honks)
[Mrs. Schröder]:
It's best you leave me here.
[Jimmy]: What was that?
- Please,
- could you leave me here?
- Right here?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- May I help you inside?
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Thank you.
- Where have you been?
- I was, um...
Get in the house.
Who the hell is that?
- (Horn blares)
- (Music playing)
[Barker]: Gather around and
behold, ladies and gentlemen,
the catch of the day!
For Neptune yields...
the treasures from his
watery kingdom:
sea bass, eel, blue crabs,
king mackerel and flounder...
Nucky.
Bill McCoy, as I live
and breathe.
- Have you been up north lately?
- Funny you should ask.
I just got back...
a little souvenir shopping.
There are things you just
can't get back home anymore.
A load's coming in
tomorrow night.
(Bell rings)
Canadian club, straight
from the distillery.
500 crates at 100 clams per.
- That's a nice even number.
- It keeps the arithmetic easy.
- I am a simple fisherman, after all.
- Not anymore, you're not.
"And he took
the loaves and fishes,
looked at his disciples
and said,
'fuck it. We're goin' into
the whiskey business".
- How much for the whole kaboodle?
- (Whistles)
It's a big city, Billy boy,
a lot of thirsty people.
40 grand.
35 and we'll do it once a week.
What does that come to a crate?
A fuck of a lot more than you're
paying for it. That's for sure.
Do we have a deal or no?
Dirty chiseler.
You'll hear from my brother
about the particulars.
Where are you going?
I thought we were having a drink.
I already got what I wanted.
What the fuck would we talk about?
- (Snickers)
- Say, Nucky,
- about that thing.
- What thing?
- The thing I wanted to talk to you about.
- Wait, I gotta get cigarettes.
(Music continuing)
(People talking quietly)
- Nucky Thompson is here.
- (Gasps)
Mr. Thompson,
what an honor.
He was a good man.
My deepest condolences.
I hadn't even realized
you knew my husband.
Oh, of course. He was a fine fellow.
Just last month we spoke.
Oh...
But the laryngectomy.
Fellas, meet the missus.
She ain't much on personality,
but she don't talk back none neither.
(Giggling)
What's the matter, kid,
never seen a stiff before?
I've seen a couple.
I'm short on time, Mickey.
What'd you want to show me?
(Sighs) So much for the niceties.
(Giggling)
(Music playing)
(Chatting,
glassware clinking)
My factory, gentlemen.
- Quite an operation.
- 10 shiners,
two shifts, 24 hours a day...
Gotta figure we're puttin' out
close to 2,000 crates a week.
And that's just for starters.
(Giggles)
- None of this is legit?
- Not once they get through with it.
One part real,
eight parts water.
You heat it up, let it cool then add
your alcohol to bring up your proof.
- Where do you get your alcohol?
- Potatoes.
You let 'em ferment.
It smell's rough,
but compared to a stiff,
it's fuckin' lilacs.
(Giggles)
After you add the alcohol,
you throw in your caramel
coloring, your oil of rye,
bourbon... depending
what you want.
- You can make scotch too?
- Naturally.
You just gotta add some
carbonyl though for the bead.
- What's that?
- The bubbles.
Higher the proof,
more bead it's supposed
to have.
Go on, bottoms up.
(Laughing)
- What the fuck's in this shit?
- Carbonyl, like I said.
Formaldehyde.
(Giggles)
- Formaldehyde, huh?
- Hey hey hey hey!
- What are you doing?
- Cocksucker!
(Gasps)
What the hell's wrong with you?
Out!
Now! Beat it.
Jimmy, out!
- Stupid bohunk.
- It was just a gag, okay?
- Yeah, you're a real pistol.
- Enough with the bohunk cracks.
- My name's Doyle now.
- What?
I changed it.
I ain't Mickey Cusick no more.
- Who's after you?
- Nobody.
- Then why Doyle?
- It sounds better is all.
A rose by any other name.
What's that supposed to mean?
Read a fucking book.
- What, are you off your nut?
- You didn't drink that piss, I did.
- You're still breathing, aren't you?
- Yeah, so's he.
That's the problem...
he's still breathing.
- He's part of my operation, kid.
- You don't need him.
What would you know about it?
What's with you? And don't tell
me it's your goddamned stomach.
You want to know what's with me?
Honestly?
- Yeah.
- Paddy Ryan.
You really expect me
to go work for that Mick?
You'd rather be my driver?
Of course not, Nuck.
It's just you... you...
make Ryan clerk?
I can run rings around that chump.
Oh, listen to Bonnie
prince Charlie.
C'mon, Nuck, you were assistant
sheriff when you were my age.
And for eight years prior I spent night
and day kissing the commodore's ass.
I've been kissing your ass
since I was 12!
And what about
the last three years?
I wanted to serve my country.
- And nearly get yourself killed.
- Sssh.
Did it ever occur how your
girl might feel about that?
- Your little boy?
- Look, if that was my fate, then so be it.
And he wants to be in politics.
You know who dies for their country, kid?
Fucking rubes, that's who.
Yeah well, I'm home now, Nuck.
- So how about it?
- Had you stayed in school,
it'd have been you
in that job and not Ryan.
All right, so you're punishing me.
Is that it?
- You're punishing me.
- I'm telling you to slow down,
get the lay of the land.
You've been home now what? A month?
Nucky, I'm not
the same kid that left.
I've seen things.
- I've done things. - Well, how are
we gonna keep you down on the farm?
- I'm serious.
- I know.
All right, look,
that's 1,000 bucks.
Go buy yourself...
- a decent suit...
- I don't want your money!
A fella hands you a grand,
you tell him to fuck himself?
You're a pip, kid, I gotta say.
Nucky, all I want
is an opportunity.
This is America, ain't it?
Who the fuck's stopping you?
Come on, let's go.
- [Mrs. Schröder]: One for you.
- [Girl]: Two!
- And two.
- Two pile of soups.
And one for you.
[Mr. Schröder]:
The automobile?
Tell me again how you came
to find yourself...
getting chauffeured
around town.
I told you.
I was walking past the church
when I felt faint.
Mr. Thompson saw me...
and was kind enough to have
his driver see me home.
C'mere.
You are a little warm.
And you're feeling better
now though, are you?
I am.
And this?
How this find its way
under the mattress?
Mommy...
That money belongs
to the children.
Like fuck it does!
Where'd you get it?
- Huh?
- Never you mind where I got it.
- By whoring yourself out?
- (Screams)
- You whore!
- (Wailing)
- You gimme that money.
- No, you sit down...
or you'll get the belt!
- Eat your food.
- I want mommy!
- (Wailing)
(Music playing)
Ahh.
Ohh.
Thank you.
[Torrio]:
This is them.
Gentlemen.
Enoch Thompson.
- (Pats)
- Okay.
- Big Jim Colosimo.
- Ah, Mr. Thompasoni.
- Nice to see you.
- Pleasure to meet you.
[Nucky]: Come on in.
Now if you come back here in July,
at the pool they have
the sea nymph festival.
- Seamina festival?
- You should come for that.
- Got them.
- [Nucky]: Like mermaids.
January 16th,
it's 8:03 pm.
Johnny Torrio meeting
with Nucky Thompson.
- Which one's Torrio?
- The gray tweed.
"Gray tweed".
(Bell dings)
We got a bead on Rothstein.
He just came in with Luciano.
This other fellow
is big Jim Colosimo.
- Come again?
- In the Homburg.
- The Hamburg?
- The Homburg.
Never mind.
He took it off.
- Who's this fella now?
- Who?
- The guy in the brown suit.
- That's the concierge.
- It's "Sierge"?
- The manager, he works here.
So the red tie, that's big Jim?
Does that man look big to you?
- How's that?
- It's Arnold Rothstein.
So it's not Colosimo?
- Arnold Rothstein.
- And Nucky Luciano.
- Lucky!
- Come again?
Lucky Luciano,
Nucky Thompson.
So... who's Colosimo?
(Growls)
- (Classical music playing)
- (Chatting)
Fella goes to divorce court.
The judge says...
"I've decided to give
your wife 25 dollars a week".
Fella says "that's mighty
swell of you, judge.
I'll try to send her a few clams
myself now and again".
- Clams?
- Money.
Clams, money, capiro?
Money, capiro?
You should put it
in some lobster too, no?
No!
No no no.
None for me.
You're a law-abiding
citizen, eh?
- No, teetotaler. Never touch it.
- Oh.
- He's the lightweight.
- I like to stay sharp at the tables.
Yeah, sharp.
The way he wins, he wants to be sharp.
Last year he clear 2 million
just of the world series alone, eh?
- Two milliones.
- And they call that one lucky.
What do you think
I'm sitting next to him for?
Hey, boy, do you have
any Caruso records?
- Enrico Caruso?
- That's fine.
- Caruso, no?
- Go find some and play it.
- Put it on, eh?
- Tell the boys.
It's like funeral music here.
- (Laughter)
- How's the chow, fellas?
- Fine.
- Delicious.
[Colosimo]:
Oh, ma, she's the best, eh?
You should come to my
restaurant sometime, eh?
- Sure.
- I treat you nice, eh?
Come on, if you like to eat,
you eat.
If you don't like to eat...
- Hmm?
- Who doesn't like to eat?
- (Singing in Italian)
- Chicago's a fine town.
It ain't New York,
that's for sure.
New York ain't New York now
with prohibition.
It will be if I have
something to say about it.
Ain't that the reason
we're all here tonight?
As you know, in light
of recent developments,
I thought it might be of mutual
benefit for you boys to meet.
All the way from chi-town out
of the goodness of his heart.
When I say mutual benefit,
I mean mine too.
I didn't come here
for the pastasciutta.
I'll be expecting
a matchmaking fee.
Of course.
See, in addition to their other enterprises,
Messrs. Rothstein and Luciano...
have significant interests in the
cabaret business back in New York.
And a man such as yourself,
with both political influence as
well as a passing acquaintance...
with the seafaring types
of the Atlantic ocean...
hey, Johnny, talk English.
Salvatore...
(Speaking Italian)
...Big business.
[Luciano]:
So what's the difference?
Go ahead, do what you
were going to do.
Could you fix us up or no?
We'll take alls we can get
up to 2,000 crates a month.
For starters.
You young fellas...
no appreciation for
the art of conversation.
All right, yeah, I gotta piss.
I apologize.
Ambition can be read
as impatience sometimes.
- Arrogance too.
- Ehh...
I have a friend...
a judge.
His daughter's wedding
is in a week.
I'd like to be able to accommodate
him and their 700 guests.
- You haven't stockpiled?
- Mmmm.
All sold already.
I'm coming up short.
Well, I have a load
coming in tomorrow.
500 crates Canadian club.
Originally I'd planned to keep it,
but seeing how I'd like to start
our relationship off on the right
foot, how about I let you have it?
- How much?
- 60 grand for the entire load.
But you use your own men
for the pickup.
Send me over the details,
we'll settle up in cash tomorrow.
All right.
All right, gentlemen,
- salut.
- Salut.
Cheers.
I was in Chicago once.
- Good steaks.
- It's all right.
A little cold,
but so is Brooklyn.
You get used to it, I guess.
Summer of '17 I passed through there
on my way to Camp Grant.
Doughboy, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- Me too.
The lost battalion.
No kidding.
How about you?
You see any action?
Little bit.
Caught some shrapnel
from a Jerry's grenade.
- Spent eight months in the hospital.
- Jesus.
Say, let me ask you something.
A guy like Rothstein,
what's a fella like that worth?
Him?
10 million at least.
- On the level?
- He's as big as they come.
Christ, Luciano's sitting
on a half a million.
I know that for a fact.
Got a spread on park Avenue.
You make that much
running card games?
Card hijacking.
He's a fucking
dope peddler too.
Did six months for pushing
heroin a couple years back.
But he only did six months?
Yeah, he bought a judge.
Oh right.
Jeez, a half million dollars...
can you imagine that?
How old is...
what is he, like our age?
22, 23 maybe.
You guys gonna get into
the liquor business too?
Losimo says no.
Too much heat from the law.
Says there's enough money
in our whorehouses.
But you don't agree?
I'm Johnny's muscle.
- Who gives a fuck what I think?
- Yeah.
[Nucky]: If you get
in trouble, don't call me.
You call my brother.
And so what you want to do...
just ask for lolly.
He'll be expecting you.
I'd wish you luck, but it
sounds like you don't need it.
- We make our own luck.
- True enough.
Hey, nice talking to you, huh?
- You too.
- Jimmy Darmody.
- Al Capone.
- All right, Al.
Mr. Thompson, thank you
very very much.
The lobsters are very good.
You paid. I'm a happy man.
Next time we come to your
place, you pay for it.
- Eh, any time.
- You kick in the clams.
- Ahhh!
- A joke, yeah.
- Thanks again. A pleasure.
- [Colosimo]: You come to Chicago,
- I fix you up.
- All right.
- (Speaks Italian)
- Jimmy, stop with the clams.
- But, you know...
- It's a joke.
Americans...
they like to make a joke.
(Piano playing)
(Laughing)
- Hey, slow down, champ.
- You buy me candy.
No Taffy.
He looks like fatty Arbuckle Jr.
- Hey!
- No no no, sweetie, sweetie.
- This way, sweetie.
- Come here.
- This way.
- Come here, Tommy.
- Stay with daddy.
- Come here.
- Maybe we should get a photo.
- No, I don't feel like it today.
James Darmody?
Ma'am.
- That's right.
- Special Agent van Alden,
bureau of internal revenue.
- Can I help you?
- Perhaps.
- Will you come with me?
- Jimmy.
It's okay, dear.
Go on home.
What's this about?
It's fine.
I'll see you at home.
Thank you, ma'am.
[Agent]:
Distinguished service cross,
battle of Saint...
- How do you say this?
- Mihiel.
Seems to me...
you're a man on the come.
I'm doing all right.
College man too...
Princeton.
For a while.
Am I in trouble or something?
Guilty conscience?
You mind telling me
what a go-getter like you
is doing working
for a crook like Thompson?
It's not like that Mr. Thompson
is a pillar of our community.
Tell it to Sweeney. We know all about him
and his little fiefdom.
The election rigging,
the graft...
None of which
we're interested in.
- What're you interested in?
- Liquor...
Its illegal importation
and manufacture.
How'd you like to come
work for the bureau?
- I got a bum leg.
- Suppose I say you don't?
You got a wife,
young son at home.
It's an honorable
profession, James,
plenty of room for advancement.
It's a godly pursuit.
Could I have one
of those cigarettes?
- Give him a light.
- Sure.
You do go to church,
don't you, Mr. Darmody?
Yeah, sure.
Well then...
you know, right?
Yeah... what?
Know what?
(Moaning)
- Giddy up, cowboy.
- Lucy, stop... stop saying that.
Come on, daddy.
- Giddy up, cowboy.
- Lucy, stop!
- What?
- With the cowboy shit.
- It's distracting.
- Okay, Nucky, come on.
- (Loud moaning)
- Oh yeah.
- (Knock on door)
- [Eddie]: Nucky!
- (Grunts)
- What?!
I heard screaming.
Are you alright?
- (Sighs)
- May I enter?
- No! What do you want?
- Steinman's on the wire.
Oh Christ.
- What?
- All right.
He is always interrupting us!
Jeez Louise.
(Growls)
What?
Screaming?
We were fucking, Eddie!
Fucking.
(Slams)
- Hello?
- It's Lolly.
Hey listen, your friend
from New York, the bankroll?
- He just took us for 90 grand.
- What?
16 hours and he wants
to keep going.
We ain't that flush
right now, Nuck.
All right, I'll be right there.
- [Nucky]: Eddie!
- Yea-ah?
- Tell Jimmy to bring the car around.
- Jimmy called to be out sick.
(Sighs) Son of a bitch.
(Door rattles)
- Lucy, open the door.
- No!
Oh, come on, baby.
I gotta get dressed.
No fucking way!
- (Sighs)
- Go spend time with Eddie.
He's obviously more
important than me.
I...
no, he's not more
important than you.
But Arnold Rothstein
and 90,000 dollars is more important!
- Open the goddamn door!
- No!
(Groans)
Why don't you go
hang out with him?
- (Lucy shouting)
- Yeah, you do it. My back.
Get in there.
Yeah yeah!
Please, Lucy, it's very
important for Eddie to come in.
- Open the...
- Open the fucking door!
(Music playing)
- Where is he?
- Eating with the Italian fellow.
I didn't want to say nothing,
but this Rothstein's a cheater.
Honestly, if he wasn't who he is, they'd
have found him in a fucking alley.
- Well, he is who he is.
- That's why I called.
You fellows ever hear of sleep?
Who can sleep
with all this excitement?
I heard luck had nothing
a lucky to do with it.
I'm a skilled player
is what he means.
- That's what I hear.
- Mmm, so?
What's all this
about cutting me off?
It's not that.
It's a small house.
We just can't handle your kind
of action right now.
Your credit's good with me.
Why don't we get to know
each other better?
I don't think I like
what I'm hearing.
Maybe you shouldn't be listening
to the grown-ups' conversations.
- How is that?
- Charlie, sit down.
Charlie... Charlie.
(Pats)
As of now, you owe me...
well, 93 grand.
Less 60 for tonight's load
knocks it to 33.
So you could keep playing then.
I don't gamble where
I don't feel welcome.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Cash him out.
Thompson, right?
I heard you're familiar
with my wife.
- Pardon?
- My wife.
Margaret...
you drove her home.
- Where'd you get that money?
- What business is that of yours?
That money belongs
to your wife.
Oh, so it was you
who give it to her.
- Here, you prick. I'm winning anyway.
- (Crowd gasps)
- [Dealer]: Hey hey!
- (Grunts)
Toss him the fuck out.
All right, we went over
the rules in the locker room.
I want a good clean fight.
No holding, no low blows,
break when I tell you.
Now touch gloves and come out fighting.
(Bell dings)
(Laughing)
Hit him!
Fucking hit him.
[Man]: Keep your right up.
Hook, jab, jab, jab.
(Shouting)
If I was you I'd bet
on the little guy.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm a fight fan.
What else?
(Laughing)
So how much you know
about this haul...
that's coming in tonight
for Rothstein?
I tell you, for a fellow good-looking
as me, I sure do get the homely girls.
- (Snickers)
- I don't mind the homely ones,
especially when they're dumb.
I love the dumb ones.
My girl is so dumb,
she thought that daylight
savings was a bank.
My girl is so dumb, she thinks
long island sound
makes a noise.
It's true!
Thank you, thank you.
That worked better than this afternoon.
You're a wonderful crowd.
My girl is so so dumb,
she thought that iceberg
was a Yiddishe name.
(Praying)
My girl is so dumb, she tried to
buy plum pudding from a plumber.
- All right, let's go.
- No, it's true.
Had him running all over town.
Something else about my girl,
she was so dumb, they finally had
to burn down the schoolhouse
to get her out
of the second grade.
They let her pose
for the class photo,
but oh boy, was she homely.
You've heard
of crocodile shoes?
Well, she had a pair...
with a complexion to match!
- (Rimshot)
- I took her to visit the zoo.
Why, the zookeeper thanked me
for bringing her back.
Lovely family though...
very nice girl.
Lovely family. Her poor father
died of throat trouble...
they hung him.
Her poor brother, lovely
chap, but he's gone too.
With good behavior, he should
be back in about 10 years.
He used to work in a bank, but no
matter how much the boss likes you,
you can't work in a bank
and take home samples.
Oh no!
Pretty fucking obvious
now, ain't it?
(Music plays)
- Okay!
- Get their guns.
You're fucking dead.
You're fucking as good as dead!
- All of youse!
- Shut your yap.
Easy easy, don't get rattled.
(Owl hooting)
- (Branch cracks)
- What's that?
What?
- (Cracks)
- That!
The fucking wind.
Relax.
(Cracking)
(Agent shouts)
The woods...
get him, get him!
Come here, you son of a bitch!
(Sighs)
- (Clicks)
- What the?
(Gunshot)
Darmody!
Jimmy!
- Did you get him?
- Yeah.
- What the fuck was that?
- The fucking deers.
Go on, get in the car.
Go on, scram!
Come on, let's go.
Beat it.
- (Tapping)
- [Man]: The court is now open.
[Woman] ¶ well, good
morning, judge... ¶
[Mr. Schröder]:
Got something to say now, huh?
¶ I said
good morning, jury... ¶
- You fucking whore!
- (Glass shatters, woman screams)
- ¶ I see you know my face, mmmmm,
mistaken surely... ¶ - (Thudding)
- [Mrs. Schröder]: Please stop!
- ¶ When I see that sign ¶
- ¶ lord have mercy on my soul...
¶ - (Child wailing)
- ¶ I couldn't budge, I hope to choke...
¶ - (Child screaming)
¶ It was all a joke,
I said good morning, judge ¶
¶ you heard me,
good morning, judge... ¶
[Judge]:
Good morning, Sophie.
- ¶ Good morning, jury... ¶
- Good morning.
(Sophie laughs)
When I see that,
what that just said,
- I can surely say...
- (Sobbing)
¶ Oh lord ¶
¶ lawd-a-mercy. ¶
(music playing)
I would love to get
married one day.
I am very very sorry.
Excuse me
for one moment.
- He is always talking on the phone.
- Hello.
- [Sheriff]: It's me.
- What?
It's me.
We got a problem.
All right, I'll be right there.
(Shouting)
Fellas, fellas,
no leads or arrests.
- How many bodies were found?
- Nothing has been confirmed at this time.
As soon as we know something,
we'll make an official statement.
Four bodies, blood everywhere.
It was like a fucking
firing squad.
No sign of the truck?
In a goddamned election year.
- The feds onto this yet?
- No.
Hands still full
at the funeral home.
Cusick's probably
having a stroke.
You know the imbecile
changed his name to Doyle?
Don't ask.
You know,
the peculiar thing is...
that at the same time
the feds are raiding Mickey,
this shit...
is happening three miles away.
Ain't that a coincidence?
So do you want
to say it or should I?
It could be Rothstein
himself set it up.
All right, so who knew
about the load?
Jimmy?
Who's mysteriously gone
missing all of a sudden.
All right, bring him in.
(Music playing)
Hey, Ange, I'm sorry.
I know it's late.
Uh, Jimmy in?
No, I haven't seen him
in hours.
I thought he was at work.
Sorry to disturb you.
When he comes home,
tell him Nucky's
looking for him.
Well, now I'm getting
concerned.
Probably ran into a friend...
war buddy maybe.
Do you think it could
have something
to do with the men
that picked him up?
Beg your pardon?
There is no comment.
Now you must stop ringing!
Cocksucking reporters.
If they want a statement,
tell them to call the Mayor.
Even reporters
ain't that stupid.
I'll give them
a statement later.
I can't get over it.
It don't make sense.
- Doesn't it?
- Come on, Eli... Jimmy?
He gives the feds
the funeral home...
- (Phone ringing)
- Throws them off the scent.
Meantime he's out
pulling this job.
- Not how, why.
- Why? Because he's greedy.
Jealous probably too.
That's the way people are, Nucky.
Arnold Rothstein.
I'm very sorry, Mr.
Thompson is not available.
He would very much like you
to call him back.
- Where are you going?
- To get some air.
(Music continues)
Mr. Thompson, I was just
coming to see you.
I'm sorry, I'm late
for a meeting.
I really just wanted
to drop this off.
I'm on my way to the hospital.
- Nothing serious, I hope?
- One of our members...
Mrs. Schröder.
She... suffered an injury.
Lost her child.
What was the manner of injury?
I'm really not
at liberty to say.
¶ Into the dark oblivion where
there ain't no use a'living ¶
¶ then you can lay me
low down in the ground ¶
¶ where not a soul
can get around ¶
¶ take away my cake,
take away my pie ¶
¶ take away my taste and even
take away my eyeball ¶
¶ but Lordy ¶
¶ but Lordy, Mr. Man ¶
¶ now don't you take away
those blues. ¶
Commodore?
Mr. Nucky
here to see you.
Well, send him in,
for God's sake.
Quite the shitstorm you got on
your hands, eh, Mr. Treasurer?
Well, good morning to you too.
These bodies in the woods
I assume belong to your
friend in New York?
(Sighs) Rothstein's men.
I don't understand
why you got involved.
Yes you do!
It was a favor to Chicago.
That plus Rothstein's
numbers were right.
Till he buggered you
in the ass.
Fucking Rothstein.
(Grunts)
By Henry fucking Ford.
Oh, I think my problems
go beyond world finance.
What a fucking night.
It's seven years today.
- Mabel.
- Oh.
I'd just gone to jail.
Not a day goes by,
I'll tell you that much.
Well, maybe she's better off.
The feds will be
all over this thing.
I can't have dead bodies lying around
on the road... bad for business.
Well, you gotta
give them someone.
Let 'em make an arrest.
It's Jimmy.
Get the fuck...
This?!
Left me holding the bag.
What a fucking little prick.
I never knew he had it in him.
Jimmy?
Eh, fucking Jimmy.
(Laughs)
Nucky.
Nuck!
- I take you back,
- Nucky,
- I give you a job...
- listen...
and this is how you
fucking repay me?!
Last night was not supposed
to happen like that, Nuck.
Make sure you mention that to Rothstein
as he's cutting your nuts off.
That's all gonna get
straightened out, I promise.
Are you that stupid?
Have no fucking idea how
in over your head you are?
- I know it's awful...
- Did I not tell you to slow down?!
I tried to give you money.
I tried...
I tried to tell you
I'm not a kid anymore!
And killing
and fucking larceny?
- That makes you a man?
- No.
(Sighs) You got brains, kid.
You had a future.
Look, I still got a future...
we both do.
The war, Nuck,
the things I did over there?
You live in a trench
for months on end.
The killing,
the smell of death...
Nucky, I'm nothing
but a murderer.
You know how many times
I went over the top?
They called me a fucking hero.
The truth is...
I didn't care anymore.
I didn't care.
You're home now.
- You got a family.
- I'm going to hell, Nuck.
- Knock it off.
- No, I am.
- You are not.
- I'm 22 years old.
I see fellas like fucking Luciano with
a fancy suit with fucking diamonds...
- is that what you want?
- That's what you want too!
That's what...
It's what we all want.
At least I got the gumption
to take it.
You'd be very foolish
to underestimate me, James.
I could have you killed.
Yeah, but you won't.
Look, you can't be
half a gangster, Nucky.
Not anymore.
Let me help you.
What the fuck is this?
It's your share for last night.
I didn't ask for this.
You didn't have to.
¶ And as the night is falling ¶
¶ I find myself recalling ¶
¶ that blissful
all-enthralling day ¶
¶ I found my love ¶
¶ in Avalon ¶
¶ beside the bay ¶
¶ I left my love ¶
¶ in Avalon ¶
¶ and sailed away ¶
¶ I dream of her ¶
¶ in Avalon ¶
¶ from dusk till dawn ¶
¶ and so I think ¶
¶ I'll travel on ¶
¶ to Avalon. ¶
(brakes squeal)
Sir, we need you to
come with us.
What're you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Get in there!
- (Singing in Italian)
- Sir!
You're making a mistake.
(Grunts)
(Singing continues)
- You get the gold?
- Are you kidding me?
(Singing continues)
(Grunts)
(Crowd gasps)
[Reporter]: The Atlantic city
sheriff's department has confirmed...
that a body found caught in a
fisherman's net this afternoon...
is that of Hans Schröder, a local man
who went missing yesterday. Stop.
Schröder, who worked
occasionally as a baker's helper,
had been sought in connection
with Saturday night's...
bloody roadside massacre. Stop.
[Cantor]: Maestro, can I have
my note, please? A note for Eddie?
¶ Ahhhh. ¶
This time it's a ballad.
¶ Jonesy used to roam ¶
¶ never stayed at home ¶
¶ he'd go out with the boys and
leave his wifey all alone ¶
¶ then the town went dry,
Jones began to cry ¶
¶ with no cafes or cabarets
I know I'll surely die ¶
¶ for weeks
it had him worried ¶
¶ but now he's feeling gay ¶
¶ I heard him tell
a friend of his ¶
¶ out on the street
today, say! ¶
¶ I never knew
I had a wonderful wife ¶
¶ until the town went dry ¶
¶ the way I spent my money
on women was a crime ¶
¶ I found that with my wife ¶
¶ I could have had
a better time ¶
¶ I'd send her to the country ¶
¶ and I'd always shout hooray ¶
¶ but I saw her picture in a
bathing suit the other day ¶
¶ I never knew
I had a wonderful wife ¶
¶ until the town
went dry. ¶