(I'LL SEE YOU IN C-U-B-A PLAYING)
(PEARL SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Look at the soldier boy!
You'd have pissed your pants
if you were wearing any.
You think it's funny?
Easy, Princeton. I was fuckin' playing.
I need the keys to the car.
I can't hear out of my ear.
Quit your bellyaching and go back to sleep.
MAN: What the hell's going on?
It's okay. I'm okay.
- You're bleeding.
- What?
(GROANS)
This is never gonna work out.
What? No! Oh, come on.
You shouldn't have.
- Now, who planned this?
- KESSLER: Nucky?
Jesus! Fuck.
How long you been standing there?
I... Very shortly.
What do you want? I was rehearsing a speech.
Well, you asked to review
the guest list for the party.
Right, yeah.
Let's hear it.
Hank Adamo, Steven Mueller...
I'm giving a speech next week
to the Restaurant Workers Association.
What I was rehearsing.
Yes. Richard Berman...
I'm going shopping.
Get something pretty.
You know, you tore me apart last night.
Jesus, Lucy.
Make sure you invite Governor Edwards.
- He will not come.
- I know. Despite that.
Can you believe they elected
that asshole Democrat no-hoper?
I booked suites
for Senator Edge and Mayor Hague.
Visiting royalty.
Edge especially.
Hand me my shoes.
Which ones?
Oh.
- Make sure Edge gets the bigger suite.
- Mmm-hmm.
He's my ticket to that
road appropriations money.
Ja.
Almost $30 million for Jersey alone.
You can bet your keister
I'm gonna get a piece of that pie.
It's an expression, "a piece of the pie."
Don't you have pie in Germany?
We have strudel.
Just make sure everybody gets laid.
EDITH: "Could it be
the beautiful young woman
"found shivering in the river
"is actually who she claims to be,
"the daughter of the Czar of Russia,
the Grand Duchess Anastasia?"
It's like a fairy tale.
"Was she assassinated
at the hands of the Bolsheviks,
"or did she masterfully escape
the fate of her doomed royal family?"
- TEDDY: Give me it.
- Mine.
- EMILY: Give it to me!
- Pipe down or you'll get a spanking.
There's no need for that now, is there?
You spoil them.
Look at this. (GASPS)
"Anastasia Romanov,
thought dead these past three years,
"could very well be the rightful identity
of Anna Anderson,
"the amnesia victim
now claiming to be the princess."
- Who's a princess?
- You are, my darling.
And I'm the Queen of England.
Really?
Where's your sense of romance, Edith?
It left along with my husband.
Read the funnies, Mama.
- Mind your manners.
- Please?
All right, quickly.
Then I've got to leave for work.
Let's see what mischief
Mutt and Jeff have been up to.
Sorry, does it hurt?
A little bit.
You should try some opium.
There's a den in Chinatown. Let me take you?
I don't know. With all those hopheads?
It's divine, it really is. For whatever ails you.
That fella, Al, he can be
really scary sometimes.
He's all right. He's just from Brooklyn, is all.
Is that where you're from?
Atlantic City.
Mmm.
Star Prairie, Wisconsin.
Right, sure.
Don't pretend like you ever heard of it.
What's it like?
Well, Grandpa was
the first white man born in town,
Pa was the first man got sent to state prison,
and Ma was the first woman
run over flat by a car.
So you could say I've got a lot to live up to.
I'll say you do.
So did you really go to college?
Where'd you hear that?
Al's always calling you Princeton.
Yeah, well, where I come from,
some people had an idea
about what I was supposed to be.
- Your pa?
- No.
That's not something he'd do.
There's a fella, kinda like...
Kinda like Torrio here.
He saw me along through the years.
That's over with now.
So what's your idea?
Beg your pardon?
About what you're supposed to be.
Oh.
That's a good question.
Hmm.
I looked at your book
while you were sleeping.
Yeah? What'd you think?
I'm heading west myself,
like the girl in the story.
California, as soon as I save up.
You're gonna be in the pictures?
Gee, I don't know. Maybe.
Well, you're certainly pretty enough.
Don't kid a kidder.
You are.
You're prettier than Lillian Gish.
I'd watch you.
Would you save me from my brutish father?
He's out of prison?
Like Lillian Gish. Broken Blossoms?
I'd sure give it a shot.
Well, then maybe I'll let you come with me.
You'll let me?
I might.
How come?
'Cause I think you need taking care of.
NUCKY: What the fuck is taking you so long?
We've been trying, Nucky.
It ain't like we haven't asked around.
Asked around? You're trying
to solve a murder, not find a lost cat.
A cat would be easier.
Nobody cares about some colored kid.
Chalky cares, so that means I care.
And you can bet your ass,
come election day you're gonna care, too.
Control Atlantic City,
you control Atlantic County.
- Control Atlantic County...
- Control New Jersey, I know.
Well, if you know, then you'd know
how much we need the colored vote.
Like it or not, they're 20% of the city, Eli.
And they vote the way he tells 'em to,
so drink your damn coffee.
They vote the way I tell Chalky to tell them.
He drives a Packard, Nucky, because of you.
He lives in a house bigger than the mayor.
You seriously think he'd ever risk all that?
- Let his people vote Democrat?
- At this point, no.
But there are limits
to what he can sell those people,
and a lynching's not one of them.
- If word got out...
- He needs you, Nuck.
- No one's ever gonna know.
- And we need him.
One hand washes the other
and both hands wash the face.
Take a lot of suds to wash Chalky's face.
(CHUCKLES)
You can wait in the hall.
I don't like that fella. I never have.
He's a good man, Halloran, ready and able.
Just step it up, will ya?
Gillian, fix it.
Let me see, darling.
Gillian?
You know, most women
are proud to be called grandma.
Not while the peaches are still in season.
I shouldn't be very long.
Take your time.
I've got my man to keep me company.
- Say goodbye to Mama.
- Bye, Mama.
Let's see here.
They make such shoddy merchandise
these days.
You know, when your daddy was a little boy,
he had a blue tin train with big round wheels.
- A choo-choo.
- That's right, it was a choo-choo train.
And it was a gift from one of my admirers.
He was in the dry goods business.
All better.
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
Where's my kiss?
You are gonna break a million hearts one day.
You know that?
Run along now. There you go.
TOMMY: I just need to move it.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Mrs. Darmody?
- Yes?
I'm a friend of James.
His friends call him Jimmy.
So who are you really?
I'm what you call
an acquaintance from New York.
That part I suspected.
- What's your name?
- Never mind my name.
Is he here or ain't he?
- He's not.
- Then where is he?
Maybe he's up your ass.
Have you considered looking there?
You got a fresh mouth for a broad.
Maybe I need you to smack it for me, right?
The roughneck bit,
is that what the little girls
are going for these days?
Filthy immigrants, Christ-killing Jews,
anarchists of every stripe.
Dangerous though they may be,
make no mistake, my brethren,
it is the coon that is the true bane
of our great nation.
(ALL AGREEING)
Up from the south they come
like so many rats,
feeding on jobs
heretofore reserved for white men.
Veterans, patriots, true Americans all,
consigned to the bread lines,
their families starving
while the nigger gorges himself.
It is our God-given right,
it is our Christian duty
to eradicate this scourge...
Nobody move!
Who's in charge here?
- State your name.
- Joseph Earl Dinler,
Grand Cyclops of the Knights
of the Ku Klux Klan, Atlantic County branch.
Lose the dunce caps.
You too, Cyclops.
You're the fella who owns
the hardware store on Pacific.
He sold me linseed oil not a month ago.
If you're here to rob us,
take what you will and leave
with what little conscience you might have.
Drop the act. You know who I am.
You're a grafter, a whoremonger,
and a bootlegger.
You're thinking of my brother.
Let's go. You're under arrest.
Everybody else, stay in your seats.
(ALL MURMURING)
What's this about?
- Being in the Klan's not against the law.
- (ALL AGREEING)
No, but stringing up darkies is.
(ALL MURMURING)
MAN: Yeah, we got our rights.
You gotta be reasonable. Huh?
Mr. Sheridan says
I can't be buying from nobody else.
You're good then,
'cause we ain't nobody else.
This is Johnny Torrio's territory now.
You should talk to Mr. Sheridan, no?
- I don't know nothing.
- What do you mean you know nothing?
You Greeks, you got intelligence.
I mean, you invented arithmetic, right?
I don't know. Yes.
Then you should know what happens next.
See, I say you gotta buy from us,
then you give me some lip,
then the next thing you know...
You all right, Demo?
You got something to say?
What happens now is I help you up.
- But not really.
- JIMMY: Al.
Please, why you do this?
Al,
- come on.
- Come on, what?
I'm in the middle of a fucking conversation.
Next I break every bottle in this fuckin' joint.
- Please, no!
- Good.
These people look thirsty,
so you'll want a big order
when the truck comes around.
Oh, yeah, if Sheridan got a problem,
(GRUNTS)
You tell him to come see me.
I'm at the Four Deuces over on Wabash.
Are you staying for supper?
(GROANS)
Demo, Demo, are you all right?
Help me get him up.
We have the pianist, the fat one.
Remember you like him.
Roast beef, rack of lamb,
oysters on the half shell, lobster,
and for the wine, I have chosen
a Château Margaux.
- Fuck is this?
- What?
This.
This, fucking lip rouge.
- I will take care of it immediately.
- God fucking damn it.
I will see that they wash them twice.
How hard do I work?
The pressure I'm under?
Is it too much to ask that
if I have a simple goddamn birthday party,
that the silverware, the crystal,
that they be clean?
Nucky, I have taken...
Can I trust you to do anything right?
The war, the anti-German bullshit,
did I not stick with you despite all that?
Yes, you...
And this is the fucking thanks I get?
This filthy piece of shit that some whore
left her cock-smeared lip rouge on?
- Do you want me to drink from this?
- No.
- Do you want my guests to drink from this?
- No, of course not.
You there, boy, scrub these goblets.
Everything...
Please do your best.
(DOOR OPENS)
Morning. How'd you sleep?
You Klan fellas,
get you in front of a crowd, can't shut you up.
In private though...
I told you 100 times.
I don't know who hung that coon.
Oh, I believe you. I really do.
Thing is, though,
I gotta be sure.
What the hell are you doing?
(DOOR CLOSES)
ISABELLE: Voilà, madame. Enjoy.
(BIDS GOODBYE IN FRENCH)
Margaret.
Yes, Madame Jeunet.
I will require you this evening. You must stay.
I'll need to make arrangements
for the children.
Rosalie, she did not have children.
Yes, ma'am.
MonsieurThompson,
tonight it is his birthday celebration.
You will deliver to Miss Danziger this dress,
to Babette's, the nightclub.
- Miss Danziger?
- The paramour.
What is it? The sweetheart of Mr. Thompson.
Yes, of course.
You will be there to Babette's by 10:00,
and then you shall wait
until after Miss Danziger does the surprise.
The silk fringe, the beading, it is very delicate,
so you must assist her in putting it on. Huh?
Very important.
Yes, ma'am.
You mentioned I must wait
until after Miss Danziger's surprise.
- What surprise is that?
- I don't know.
This is why it is the surprise.
(GREETING IN FRENCH)
You wanna branch out, that's jake with me,
so long as it puts money in my pocket.
But what I don't need, at any price,
is a fuckin' headache.
I'm gonna straighten it out, I promise.
How? By smackin' around bartenders
for the next six months?
This fuckin' Sheridan is a pain in my ass.
I'm gonna talk to him, John,
soon as he gets here,
work out an accommodation.
Believe me, you're gonna be rolling in it.
I'm going.
I got a plantar's wart on my foot.
It hurts like a son of a bitch.
You see that?
'Cause he knows I can handle it.
Or maybe he actually has a plantar's wart.
Don't be jealous 'cause I'm moving up, pal.
I got big coat tails.
I move up, you're coming along for the ride.
You got me all wrong.
I'm just passing through.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
It's them.
Some free advice.
You don't invade a country all at once.
You take it over one piece at a time.
Act nice, negotiate for a portion.
In a couple of months, you expand.
Then, before you know it,
you're controlling his entire territory.
- Mr. Sheridan?
- Who the fuck are you?
Al Capone. This is Jimmy Darmody.
Where the fuck's Torrio?
Mr. Torrio sends his regrets.
He had some pressing business to attend to.
What does he call this?
He says you should talk to me.
I gotta say this is very insulting.
I come all the way down here in the snow.
Trolleys ain't even running.
Can we offer you anything?
Some coffee, some whiskey?
No.
Forget California. Today, I'm heading east.
Chinatown.
I'll see you later, okay?
So how's the Greek fella?
Probably at the dentist
getting the shoe leather out of his chops.
That fella gotta learn some manners.
I'd say a lot of fellas do.
Are you talking about me, pally?
Mr. Sheridan, we asked you down here
to work out a compromise.
The way that we see it,
Greektown is big enough for all of us.
SHERIDAN: You New York fellas
make me laugh.
You come out here from Brooklyn
or wherever the fuck,
and you act like you own the town.
- He's from Jersey.
- I don't give a fuck where he's from, boy-o.
He's in Chicago now.
Mr. Sheridan, I didn't mean any disrespect.
- The point is that we have ambition...
- The point is this.
You stay the fuck out of Greektown
or there's gonna be trouble.
We're already in Greektown, sonny.
We've been in Greektown
since Colosimo took over.
Maybe you didn't hear, but Colosimo retired
on account of that bullet in his fuckin' head.
Johnny Torrio, also from Brooklyn,
he runs things now
and he's taking over your territory.
And what? There's no room for negotiation?
There might be.
How's about he take a piece of my action?
How much?
- Ten percent.
- Twenty-five.
All right, fine.
Let's call it 50.
Fifty?
You heard me.
I don't want any trouble, okay?
Tell Torrio he gets what he wants.
Fuckin' loudmouth. I knew he'd cave.
That's one way of reading it.
I was born in Elgin, Texas.
My daddy taught himself the carpenter trade
doing for the black folk there.
And I tell you,
anything that man put his hand to,
table, chair, wedding chest,
he make that wood sing.
Now one day, a man,
Mr. T.O. Purcell, come round.
He a white man, own his own store,
a stable, hotel.
He say to my daddy,
"I hears you the finest carpenter in Elgin."
My daddy tell him,
"Well, I can't say one way or the other,
"but I knows a bit about somethin'."
So Mr. T.O. Purcell take my daddy
to this house he was building,
biggest house in town.
They walk in there, say,
"This here gonna be the library.
What you think 'bout that?"
My daddy say,
"Well, I thinks you need some bookcases."
"Well then, that's what
I want you to make me."
Ten month my daddy work there.
And then when he finished,
he bring me around.
"Mr. Purcell, this here's my boy.
I'd like to show him what I done."
"Come on in through the front door."
Just like that.
And we did.
When I seen them bookcases,
all carved with scroll and flowers,
baskets of fruit,
little angels floating in the corner,
that was the most beautiful thing I ever seen.
About a month later,
another man come round.
"I seen what you did for T.O.
"I can't let that old dog top me.
"You come round my house
and I'll show you what I need."
My daddy go with him to the edge of town.
Wasn't nothing there but six white men,
12 foot of rope,
and the pepper tree they hung him from.
These here are my daddy tools.
What are you gonna do with them?
Well,
I ain't buildin' no bookcase.
And now for your edification and enjoyment,
we take you to Ancient Rome.
(MEN CHEERING)
(MEN WOLF-WHISTLING)
(MAN CHATTERING IN FRENCH)
Witness the ritual bathing of Aurelia,
mother of the great emperor, Julius Caesar.
Behold her palace slaves who have no choice
but to submit to her every imperial wish.
It wasn't the Klan.
- How do you know?
- He told me.
And you believe him?
There's a point which if a man
still sticks to his story,
that's a man that's telling you the truth.
We passed that point about 10 minutes ago.
CROWD: Surprise!
Oh, my God! What?
I had no idea.
(BAND PLAYING JAZZ MUSIC)
What do you tell a woman
with two black eyes?
Nothing.
She's already been told. Twice.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Now that's one way to deny 'em the vote.
- I thought you were all for that, Senator.
- I am, on the record.
So long as they vote Republican.
We Democrats feel the same way.
May that never fucking happen.
It is happening, boys.
32 states already ratified?
Those suffragettes did their job.
I think they all need a good rogering.
- Right, dearie?
- I know I do.
It's nothing to be afraid of.
You just gotta give 'em what they want.
- Who knows what that is?
- It doesn't matter.
Women don't have the mind for politics.
You're assuming they have minds at all.
I have brains, you know.
- NUCKY: Buttercup...
- No, no, let her speak.
- Lucy...
- Let the little lady be heard.
Please, angel, tell us your thoughts
on the League of Nations.
- The what?
- The...
- (MEN LAUGHING)
- NUCKY: The League of Nations.
There was a big meeting
in Paris three weeks ago.
Well, I don't know about that league thing,
but Paris sure sounds swell.
You wanna take me, daddy?
Now there's a thinking woman.
- Go get me a fresh one, okay?
- Okay, baby.
Perhaps she's not the best example.
Relax, will ya? I've been dealing with mugs
like this my whole life.
I asked around, Al.
This Sheridan is a serious fella.
No offense, but these micks,
they come on strong,
but it's just the booze talking.
Now if they were Sicilian,
it'd be a different story.
MAN: Gentlemen?
We're ready for you.
I gotta say thanks, pal.
I know this can't be cheap.
Springing for some new threads?
This is mighty white of you.
A little fruity, but we're businessmen, right?
Gotta look the part.
You get that over there?
The Meuse-Argonne.
It's been killing me lately.
Them heinies, cut us both up. Huh?
- Lousy bastards.
- Right.
The slim cut, very à la mode.
That means right on the money.
The wide shoulders,
a very masculine silhouette.
What does the gentleman think?
Wife's gonna shit.
Yes, please. Keep it coming. That's right.
Mrs. Schroeder, welcome.
Mr. Thompson, happy birthday.
Why, thank you.
Oh.
I'm to deliver this gown to Miss Danziger.
Oh. Of course.
I'll put it in the dressing room for you.
I trust Isabelle is treating you all right?
Madame Jeunet? Yes, she is.
Is that what she makes you call her?
There's the birthday boy.
Enjoying yourself, Walter?
I'll soldier on as best I can.
May I present Senator Walter Edge
up from Washington,
and the honorable Frank Hague,
mayor of Jersey City?
Gentlemen, Mrs. Margaret Schroeder.
- Mrs. Schroeder.
- Ma'am.
- A pleasure, I'm sure.
- May I get you a drink?
- Whiskey, gin?
- Thank you, no. I don't drink.
Mrs. Schroeder is a member
of the Women's Temperance League.
Oh.
A fine organization.
It is.
Well, I guess I stepped in it. (LAUGHS)
You're not a suffragette, I hope.
- Not officially at least.
- Another one, eh?
I come from a country
where women already have the right to vote.
In fact, in most civilized countries
women are afforded that privilege.
Well, in this country,
we're simply trying to protect women
from the hard truths of life.
By denying them the right to take
a meaningful part in it?
It's a shame you see it that way.
It isn't just me, sir.
It's most women who'd like the right to vote.
And as you've learned, if you withhold from
a woman something she deeply desires,
then she'll surely find a way
to withhold something that you desire.
And what might that be?
Alcohol.
Well, now, they haven't done
a very good job of it now, have they?
Well, now, the party's only just started.
Walter, I think you've met your match.
Mrs. Schroeder,
I'll see you to the dressing room.
- Gentlemen.
- Ma'am.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, Miss Edith Day.
(VOCALIZING)
I hope you're not offended by all the drinking.
- Old habits die hard.
- If they die at all.
That's a very practical perspective.
I'm a very practical woman.
Well, then, I suppose we should dance.
(WOMAN SINGING
IN MY SWEET LITTLE ALICE BLUE GOWN)
Thank you, Mrs. Schroeder.
It's always a pleasure.
It was all mine.
Your attention. Your attention, please.
Hit it, fellas.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
ALL: (SINGING) For he's ajolly good fellow
For he's a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Welcome, boys.
Al here?
Be back later.
What about the other one? Jimmy?
We don't cater to poofs, fellas.
He recommended one of the girls.
I forget her name.
Pearl probably.
MAN: Yes, yes.
That's her.
Gotta face facts, Nuck.
We have a Democrat for governor now.
These matters have to be finessed.
And in the meantime, what?
I lose my road money to Frank?
People up north don't need roads?
Actually, Frank, they don't.
Relax, boys,
there's plenty of dough for everyone.
Well, I'll take mine now.
There are limits, Nucky. Jesus!
You can't expect to have everything.
Is that what I told you when I put you
in the Governor's Mansion?
- Nucky...
- And in the Senate?
Have I not thanked you enough?
You were the best campaign manager
I've ever seen. Hell, that ever was.
But you've got to understand,
this is complicated.
I've got hotels that no one can get to
except by stinking train
because the roads to Atlantic City
are rivers of fucking mud.
We need paved highways
so cars can come and go.
"So cars can come and go."
Is that what you're worried about?
- And trucks.
- Trucks full of liquor.
What's that, lemonade in your hand?
I'm just proposing we call a spade a spade.
Fine. How's this?
You don't need the road money up north
and you fucking know it.
The people of Jersey City
need highways just as...
Jersey City, my balls!
You're looking for a payoff
so you'll back the fuck away.
So why not save us all time
and give me a number?
I'll need to do some calculations.
Fine. Finally.
You fucking Democrats, boy.
Now, now, let's not let party politics
affect what's best for the people.
Jesus, Walter, have you packed
for the White House already?
No, but when I'm there,
maybe I can help you
by controlling Governor Edwards.
Maybe?
Oh, now, let's not let our best days
be behind us, shall we?
I'm through with this champagne.
What's your pleasure, Senator?
I'll have a Pimm's Cup.
Eddie.
I am so sorry.
We have no Pimm's Cup tonight.
What do you mean?
There is no Pimm's.
Name anything else, Senator.
Well,
I'll have a brandy.
Ja.
Why is there no Pimm's?
EDGE: Easy, will you?
Like I said,
can't expect to have everything. Hmm?
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
You all set?
What's your hurry?
This ain't a love story, bub.
You're nice, classy.
You don't even seem like a whore.
Thanks.
Your friend there, Jimmy, he got good taste.
I'll pass on the compliment.
Come here.
I gotta get back downstairs.
Let me look at you.
Something to remember you by.
No kissing.
No, I know.
Jesus, you're like a fucking angel.
(SCREAMING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
Yeah, okay. Come on, let's go.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MAN: I need a pack of smokes and a paper.
I'd have loved to have been there.
I just didn't think you'd want
this kind of news on your birthday.
I don't want it the day after my birthday either.
I didn't know
he'd take that fella's finger, Nuck.
(KESSLER CLEARING THROAT)
For your signature.
Senator Edge ran up quite a bill.
Eighteen hundred dollars?
He said to thank you for a wonderful time.
ELI: Do I return the Klan guy's ring?
Or is that adding insult to injury?
- How's she doing?
- The doctor's given her a sedative.
Can't I see her?
She needs to sleep, kiddo.
Is it bad?
Go on.
I'll put these in a vase.
Cheer up.
It happened to me. I'm still beautiful.
It wasn't me made a muck of it.
You dopes killed the wrong coon.
- "He drives a Packard," you said.
- MICKEY: But it wasn't Chalky.
You hung a fella who works for him.
He got the message, didn't he?
He probably crapped his drawers.
Then why is he still operational?
It was your idea in the first place.
How should we know?
Where's our dough anyways?
I need a new topcoat.
- Which brother is this now?
- Teo.
Teo, Leo, Ignacious.
What are youse, all named after popes?
What of it? You don't like God or somethin'?
Take it easy.
Seven thousand clams, Mickey.
Where's our fuckin' money?
Okay, okay.
I'll get it.
From where?
What do you say I get you a deal?
Put three grand in your pockets?
Yeah, I'm listening.
Nucky Thompson.
One of his ward bosses makes
a nice fat collection by The Ritz every Friday.
- Nucky's joint?
- Nucky's money.
It's candy from a baby, I tell ya.
All right, you dope out a plan.
But you botch it up, my brother's gonna
give you a haircut you'll never forget.
What's this?
From Nucky Thompson.
(SHOWGIRLS CHATTERING)
Waiting for someone?
Yeah, actually.
I've been waiting to see you.
Here I am. What do you want?
Cat got your tongue?
You've been following me around for days.
You must have some idea.
I think you already know what I want.
No, dear.
I only know what I want.
Meet me here after the last show.
- Madame Jeunet?
- One minute.
Yes? What is it?
Oh.
I'm done.
9:00 a.m. Tomorrow for inventory.
Yes, ma'am.
Good evening, Madame Jeunet.
(BIDS GOODBYE IN FRENCH)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(PRETTY KITTY KELLY PLAYING)