There was a hijacking
in the woods last January.
Nobody was supposed
to get hurt.
Then why did they?
I can give you the ringleader.
You can just ask him.
- What's his name?
- Jimmy Darmondy.
Somehow, James, we've all been
managing to get along without you.
Your family as well.
Nucky Thompson didn't get
where he is by being naive.
- He could stop giving me money.
- What about Jimmy?
I would have thought
he'd send something.
I told you no doctors, damn it.
Maybe you got worms.
Nucky Thompson come by?
No sir, he sent Mr. Boyd
on by with your envelope.
Getting too big
for his britches.
What is this obsession
with this Schroeder character?
You requisitioned the
immigration file on his wife?
I've been waiting for
a report on Mr. Darmondy.
- I'm with his wife right now.
- No you're not, Charlie.
You're with his mother.
I need you to come home, James.
There are things I may require that
I'm uncomfortable asking of Eli,
particularly with
the election coming.
He invited me.
The name should be on the list.
Tell me something
else while you're at it.
Like how you propose to take
care of Harding's lady trouble.
Name's Nan Britton.
I'll bring her to A.C.
Put her up till November.
I'm prepared to throw the Jersey
delegation behind Harding.
You could wait in the hall.
I don't like that fella.
I never have.
He's a good man, Halloran.
What the hell are you doing?
There's been a incident.
I prefer to rely only on you.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
It's crazy.
While it's happening you don't
think you'll ever forget it.
Then once it's over,
you can barely recall a thing.
But it's them, right? You're sure
these are the guys who held you up?
- Absolutely.
- These three definitely.
This is the little prick
who spit in my face.
The D'Alessio brothers...
a family of dagos out of Philly.
Second-story men
who graduated to stick ups.
They robbed Bookbinder's
in '17, the restaurant.
Killed two customers,
shot a waiter in the face.
- Jesus Christ.
- Little bastard called me fat.
They're fucking killers, George.
Sounds to me
like you got off easy.
Why, sure. I was just...
I need to talk to my brother.
Feel better, eh?
These fucking guineas...
They're desperados, Nuck.
We gotta track 'em down
and squash 'em
before they spill more blood.
It's not just blood
I'm worried about;
it's ink.
You see the paper today?
June doesn't like to upset me.
Fletcher, this reformer
running for Mayor...
He gave an interview
alleging corruption
in both the Mayor's
and the Sheriff's office.
He mentioned me by name?
"Has Mayor Bacharach even questioned
what Sheriff Eli Thompson was doing
at an illegal casino at 3:00 A.M.?"
So I was there. So what?
How's he know I wasn't
answering a call?
Because he knows, Eli.
Everybody does.
It just never made
the paper before.
Fuck 'em.
Let them write what they want.
The election, Eli...
We gotta keep the tide
flowing in our direction.
I'll get out then,
press the flesh,
drum up some support.
What about your spleen?
Dr. Surran says you should rest.
How do you rest your spleen?
- Come on, Grant.
- That water was cold.
Let's tell the ladies.
Oh, that was amazing!
Way out there.
Do you believe in love at
first sight, Mrs. Schroeder?
It's a rather romantic notion.
It happened to me
the day I saw Warren.
Senator Harding?
I was 16,
and he was the handsomest man
I'd ever met.
Of course he wasn't
Senator yet.
He ran the newspaper
back in Marion.
Houdini's brother...
His name is Hardeen.
And when I first heard Harding,
I thought it was him
running for president.
He loves me
and he loves his baby daughter.
But America needs him
and so I have to sacrifice.
Marguerite.
- Good morning.
- Madame Jeunet.
This is a friend of
mine, Miss Nan Britton.
She needs a few outfits
for the season.
C'est gentil.
We exist to oblige.
Maryska.
Maryska!
See the mademoiselle
to the dressing room.
This way.
A cow waiting to be milked...
the Polish girl.
No grace, no charm.
Well, I imagine
she's still learning.
A head like a cabbage.
But she will work
for pennies.
You see what I am reduced to?
Is business slow, ma'am?
My dear Marguerite,
how you have blossomed.
Mr. Thompson is quite
generous with his attentions.
He does treat me well.
The finest things
for the finest ladies,
as it must be here.
But the cost is very high,
and then on top I must pay.
- Pay whom?
- Mr. Thompson of course.
Oh, you mean the city.
I am told now
I must pay double.
Everyone must.
I have saved nothing,
Marguerite.
All to run the shop.
I am a woman alone.
You understand this.
Can you not speak
with your alderman?
You can speak for me...
to the man who gives you
his attention.
I... I wouldn't know
what to say.
Say that he is handsome;
How happy he makes you;
And how can you buy the things
that make you pretty for him
if there is no belle femme?
Help me, Marguerite.
You have power
you do not suspect.
Oh bonjour, madame.
Leave no stone unturned.
You and your men
wire every department
from Philly to Pittsburgh.
- You should also write to...
- Nucky.
Jesus. A little notice
would've been nice.
- I sent a telegram.
- We have received nothing.
I will call the
Western Union to complain.
I'd offer you coffee,
but it looks like
you've already helped yourself.
The train... the dining
car was out of service.
- You haven't been home?
- I thought I should see you first.
- Have them send up a steak.
- Ja.
So you're here.
- I assume you've accepted my offer?
- With conditions.
My friend Richard Harrow...
You met him in Chicago.
- The man in the iron mask?
- He's a war hero.
- I'd like him to join me.
- What's under there?
He's missing
his cheekbone, his jaw.
Basically the whole left side
of his face is gone.
And he's still alive?
Medicine, huh?
A lot of fellas still alive
probably shouldn't be.
Well, I know a few myself.
- The D'Alessio brothers out of Philly.
- Another condition:
We keep what we discuss
only between us.
Wait outside.
So these are the guys
that robbed the casino?
And O'Neill as well.
Ignacious, Sixtus, Leo...
- They're all named after Popes.
- Write the Vatican,
see if they know
where they are.
When I find them...
What do you want me to do?
You need me to spell it out?
I'd like to hear you say it.
Why?
Politician to the last, huh?
What, you don't say it, you
don't have to deny it later?
Or are you just trying
to kid yourself?
About what?
The fact that
you're a murderer, Nuck.
That is what you
want me to do, right?
Kill them?
Yes.
Even the kid?
I'm gonna go eat my steak.
- Gentlemen.
- A.R.
These are the fellas
I told you about.
This is Leo D'Alessio,
- his brother Ignacious.
- And Mickey Doyle.
An honor, Mr. Rothstein.
So you've heard of me.
- Naturally. Who ain't, huh?
- Yeah.
And what is it you've heard?
- Good stuff, you know.
- That I'm honest?
That you'll always
get a square deal?
Sure, that's why we're here.
A reputation takes
a lifetime to build
and only seconds to destroy.
I understand you're interested in
the liquor business.
We's interested in makin' dough.
Piles of it.
Eight ball, $500.
You break.
There are two ways
to make money
in the alcohol business.
One is to take cheap rotgut
whiskey, dilute it and sell it.
- I was doing good with that myself.
- That's the stupid way,
in which I have no interest.
There's a growing demand for good
whiskey in the United States.
And I'm not talking
about the swill
you stirred up
in your chamberpot.
I'm talking about the
best scotch from Britain.
There's a fortune to be
made from importing it.
It'll be the chic thing to have
good whiskey when you have guests
and the rich will vie
with one another to serve it.
I want to set up a business
for importing scotch.
We'll have ships
with crews we can trust
who'll sail it from
the distilleries in Europe
and unload it outside
the three-mile limit.
All we have to do
is smuggle it ashore.
That's where you mugs come in.
The ports of Atlantic City
are ideal for distribution
to the entire eastern seaboard.
The only problem is the man
who runs that city.
Normally I'd make a deal
with such a man,
cut him in as a partner,
but I find Nucky Thompson
to be greedy and unreasonable.
Nothing a bullet in the eye won't fix.
If you'll each sign
those forms,
I'll take it as your acquiescence
to our new arrangement.
- What are they?
- Life insurance policies.
There's a half a million
on each of you.
You'll be handling
large amounts of my money,
gentlemen.
It's my assurance
you won't chisel me.
Think of it as an incentive
not to screw
things up.
I'll show you out.
Do you know
what the nice thing is
about the Bronx zoo, Charlie?
There's bars between you
and the monkeys.
Finally asleep.
I could've read them
some more of this.
You seem to be
enjoying it yourself.
"The wonderful love magnet...
As long as I carry it,
every living thing I meet
will love me dearly."
That would make your election
easier, wouldn't it?
- Certainly cheaper.
- Is winning expensive?
Not as expensive as losing.
And will Mr. Harding
be president?
That depends.
Are you planning to vote for him?
I've perhaps seen him in not
the most flattering light.
- You mean the girl.
- Her name is Nan.
If we only elected good men,
we'd never have leaders.
If not good, then what
should they be?
Useful... to those
who support them.
I was speaking with
madame Jeunet today.
- Oh?
- She says she's going to lose the shop.
It's a pricey location.
Apparently she's having
trouble with the city.
Then she should talk
to her alderman.
She did. It didn't help.
Maybe there's something the
County Treasurer could do.
- Did she ask you to bring this up?
- No.
Then why are
we discussing it?
She showed me a kindness
and I thought to return it.
I made her hire you, Margaret.
Kindness didn't come into it.
Then you should recompense her
for the burden
you made her carry.
What did she tell you exactly?
Only that the money
she pays has increased
and it's more
than she can afford.
Then she shouldn't be doing
business in Atlantic City,
- Because that's what it costs.
- But if you set the price...
Margaret, this is not
a suitable topic.
I wasn't aware of that.
You're aware now.
Will you not be staying?
I have an early meeting.
I painted this last October.
- She was an actress in the vaudeville.
- Huh.
It's pretty.
This...
There's a lyrical quality.
It's reminiscent of Mary Cassatt.
Do you think your friend
is visiting soon?
The art dealer?
Oh, he's abroad
at the moment... Paris.
The city of light.
Oh, God damn it.
- I broke the cork.
- Here.
There.
Oh my, you uncivilized artists.
1918...
That's the year we met you.
Alright, save some
for your jealous husband.
Mm.
Come.
It's okay, darling.
I don't bite.
- I, uh...
- Everyone in Paris is doing it.
Hello?
Ange?
Angela, it's me.
Hello?
It's Jimmy.
It's me.
Why is the door locked?
We've had intruders
in the neighborhood.
- Where's the baby?
- He's sleeping.
Jimmy, my God.
You're having a party?
We're just visiting.
May I pour you some wine?
I heard that's
against the law now.
Well, it is getting late
and, uh, you have
that sitting in the morning.
Oh yes.
A wedding portrait.
Lithuanian couple.
Well, it was nice
to see you, old boy.
Welcome home again.
- You should have told me you were coming.
- I did.
Goddamn Western Union!
- What... what are you doing?
- I'm kissing you.
Wait... You show up
out of nowhere,
not a phone call for months...
Ange, look, I'm home okay?
For good.
- You're hurting me!
- I missed you.
Yes, I will.
Thank you for bringing this
to my attention.
They only had the plain ones...
That was Western Union.
They just got a call
from Nucky Thompson's butler
inquiring about a wire
from James Darmody.
They said it was
passed on to you.
- Oh my God.
- What is the meaning of this?
I have it here.
- I was going to give it to you.
- Then why didn't you?
"Arriving Thursday,
11:00 A.M. train."
- That was yesterday.
- I'm sorry, it slipped my mind.
You're either
incompetent or a liar.
I won't stand for it
either way, Agent Sebso.
- We've been so...
- I will not stand for it either way!
Why was this hidden?
Because I'd like
to keep my job.
Supervisor Elliot...
He thinks we're being obsessive
about the Hans Schroeder case,
about Nucky Thompson.
We have a witness
that can place
Darmody at the scene
of the murders.
I wasn't thinking.
You kill a snake by cutting
off the head, Agent Sebso.
The supervisor?
Nucky Thompson!
Darmody gives him up,
this entire city,
this Sodom, will be
cleansed all at once.
There's coal in the ground,
lumber in the forests,
cattle in the fields.
What sound does the cow make?
- Moo!
- That's right.
You ride that train,
you look out the window,
you don't see anything but
opportunity from coast to coast.
And now he's returned to this one.
And now I'm home, Ange,
where I belong.
When you feel like showing up.
I had business out west.
I told you, but that's...
that's all taken care of.
So now what?
Now our prospects
are looking up.
- Nucky made me an offer.
- Assistant clerk?
Let's just say that we're out
of this dump in no time flat.
Marven Gardens, those
beach houses on Ventnor...
How does that sound?
Hello?
Okay okay.
Sweetie, come here.
Yeah, just keep him there.
Bye.
- Mush!
- No, no mush today.
Eggs.
- Who was that?
- It was my mother.
I got to go see her.
Come on, champ.
What are you doing?
I'm making more coffee.
Let's have another baby.
What do you say?
You want a little brother, champ?
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
Then it's settled.
Your stomach is growling.
Are you hungry?
I wouldn't mind
eating you for lunch.
Maybe for dessert.
Got any coffee left?
I can manage that.
- Oh! Fuck!
- I wasn't sure if you took cream.
It's not there, dear.
- You fucking twat.
- Hey!
That's my mother
you're talking to.
My apologies.
So you're Luciano.
My mother told me
a lot about you.
We're very close, Charles.
Plus we have a mutual friend
in Chicago.
Al Capone says hello.
That's a lot of baloney.
Capone's no pal of mine.
You're right.
Actually he didn't say hello.
He said I should blow
your fucking brains out.
I'd consider it a great
favor if you didn't.
Get dressed.
We're gonna take a ride.
- To where?
- Someplace they won't find you.
Come on, move it.
It don't gotta be
like this, you know?
Tell Nucky I'll talk to A.R.,
call off the D'Alessios.
- What?
- We'll cut him in.
There's plenty
to go around for every...
Drop the gun!
Now.
James Darmody,
you're under arrest.
What are you smiling at?
You fellas.
- Youse are a sight for sore eyes.
- Hands on the wall.
Fuck.
Mid-July and they're
all over the place already.
How am I supposed
to compete with this guy?
That's the spirit, Mr. Mayor.
I want these placards
taken down.
Any shop that posts one
gets a $25 fine.
- Can we do that?
- We can do whatever we want.
- When's Eli coming back?
- Stitches opened up.
Doc Surran said this'll probably
set him back another month.
It gets better
and better, doesn't it?
He's left a big void,
I'll tell you that.
He's not dead, Halloran.
I know, but the men,
the other deputies,
they're gonna need
some guidance...
Schedules, assignments,
that kind of thing.
Can't Eli handle that?
Not in the state he's in.
What are you trying to say?
That I think
I should be in charge.
- Oh, you do?
- I've got the most experience
and the other fellas
look up to me.
Fine, you're acting Sheriff.
Really?
- Should I reconsider?
- No no.
No.
Thanks, Nucky.
I know we've had
our differences,
but I want you to know
that I'm here for you,
now and in November.
What does that mean?
Have you thought
about the future?
It certainly sounds
like you have.
In regards to Eli, I mean.
The election's right around the
corner and he's hurt, weak,
the reformers
are alleging corruption.
I mean you've seen the
articles yourself, right?
All I'm saying is that
I'm at your service
should you need.
- I was at the picture show.
- Which one?
- "Wagon Tracks."
- What was the plot?
Are you sure you want
me to ruin the ending?
We can do this all day,
Mr. Darmody.
It feels like
we already have been.
You're proposing
that on the night
of January 17, 1920,
you were in
a moving picture show
from 7:00 P.M.
until 11:30 P.M.?
That's right.
The running time of the film
is only 78 minutes.
I fell asleep.
You have a child
out of wedlock.
Is his mother not fit to marry?
That's none of your business.
What's the name of the
William S. Hart character in the movie?
- Buckskin? Buck-something.
- You're not sure?
We're engaged.
We're going to be married.
Your aim at making her
a respectable woman.
How do you know Hans Schroeder?
I don't know Hans Schroeder.
- Mrs. Schroeder? Margaret?
- I don't know these people.
Lucy Danziger, she's a
dancer at Ziegfeld Follies.
- You know her?
- It's Nucky's girlfriend.
Then what is the relationship
between Mr. Thompson
and Mrs. Schroeder?
You want to know who Nucky
Thompson is fucking,
why don't you ask him?
This shipment of alcohol
that Mr. Thompson sold
to Arnold Rothstein,
the shipment that was
being transported
the night of January 17th...
- "Wagon Tracks."
- How do you know Al?
- I don't know any Al.
- From Chicago?
You've got it all mixed up, officer.
Did Mr. Thompson have
Hans Schroeder murdered
because he's in love
with Schroeder's wife?
The men in the woods...
How many did you kill?
I went to the movies.
I fell asleep.
I got up. I walked home.
I went to bed.
You wanna charge me, charge me.
I've got nothing else to say.
I thought you might find
some satisfaction
in living long enough to see
your son grow into a man.
- You don't got anything on me.
- Don't I?
Billy?
- Jimmy?
- Jesus Christ.
They were gonna send me
up the river, Jimmy.
- What did you say to them, Billy?
- Fucking Rahway.
- What'd you tell them?
- Jimmy!
- Billy, what'd you say to...
Fuck!
The old days, it was different.
You could count on people
to vote the party line.
Now these democrats come along,
make big promises.
And you're concerned.
Enough not to take
anything for granted.
I wish there was a way
I could help.
There is.
You can help us get
the women's vote.
Shouldn't you wait until the
amendment actually passes?
I'm an eternal optimist.
Speak to your friends,
the Temperance League,
other women's organizations.
I'm not much of an orator.
I've seen you speak.
You comport yourself very well.
When was that?
At my birthday
with Senator Edge.
Oh, that was merely banter.
He's a United States Senator and
you wiped the floor with him.
Seriously, would you
be willing to speak
on behalf of the party?
- I suppose so, but...
- But what?
Do you not wish me
to dress well?
What do you mean?
Do you not wish me
to look attractive?
Of course I do.
I mean you are,
whatever you're wearing.
- Nucky, you have a call.
- All right.
Madame Jeunet knows
what suits me.
She knows how to
make me look pretty.
She's the only one I trust.
That's why you want her
to stay in business?
Why didn't you just say
that in the first place?
I didn't want you to know
how selfish I was.
I never hold that
against anyone.
Hello?
Today?
- Thank you.
- 10 minutes.
Did you talk to Angela?
She's aware of the situation.
D'Alessios... They're being
backed by Rothstein and Luciano.
From the horse's mouth.
Luciano spilled it to me
before I was arrested.
Can you bail me out?
Five counts of murder...
There is no bail.
- Would you get me a lawyer at least?
- For what?
You know, to talk to,
plan a strategy.
It's a waste of money.
Then, uh...
Call my dad.
Can't he help?
Your dad?
Are you that nervous?
This kid, Billy Winslow...
He's gonna testify, Nuck.
- So I've heard.
- So I'm staying here?
Is that what you're saying?
You said you were going
to take care of this.
I am. All I'm saying
is the legal system's
not your ticket to freedom.
Uh, yes, I'm still
on the line, operator.
Thank you.
Sir.
Nelson, I was in a command meeting.
What's the hubbub?
We've arrested
James Darmody, sir.
What? When?
Last night.
He returned from Chicago.
- Did he talk?
- No, but he's aware we have his accomplice.
- Either way, the road leads to Thompson.
- Wonderful, Nelson.
Terrific. It's a real shot
in the arm for the Bureau.
Thank you for
your confidence, sir.
Keep up the good work.
- What did he say?
- He was pleased... very much so.
Congratulations, sir.
I didn't do it alone.
I'm sorry about the telegram.
That was very foolish of me.
It was, but people
make mistakes.
A man needs to have the
courage of his convictions.
I knew we'd get
Darmody eventually.
You were right.
Hmm.
This witness, Billy Winslow...
You think it's safe
to keep him here?
What'd you have in mind?
Move him north pending trial?
Federal jail
in Manhattan maybe?
Keep him out
of Thompson's reach.
Jesus Christ, will you
see a doctor already?
Stubborn as a mule.
Shut up and get him a drink.
I'm fine, thank you.
You look like shit.
Well, your time comes,
you just have to
accept your situation.
Are we talking about you or me?
This Fletcher
and these fucking democrats.
And your Sheriff
is out of commission now too?
It's not so easy, is it?
Nice that you can
still find joy.
Five years in jail...
Can you blame me?
One of us had to go.
You knew that.
- I had no choice.
- Neither did I.
Which is why we made a deal,
so let's put it to bed
where it belongs.
We're in trouble.
Mayor Bacharach...
He's weak and losing ground.
Even the fucking dog is sick.
Well, what do you
have on Fletcher?
Nothing.
He's clean.
What does he want?
He wants to be Mayor.
Fucking boy scout.
Well, replace him.
What do you mean?
Bacharach.
Run somebody else for Mayor.
People want change,
give it to them.
Or at least pretend
to give it to them.
What do I do about Eli?
Replace him too.
You son of a bitch.
I'm dying.
There's no time
to be sentimental.
I still can't decide.
On you every dress
is a joy to behold.
They're all so plain.
I'll need something special
to wear to the inaugural.
I think for now though just
something to wear around town.
Oh, I do so love this.
Mademoiselle's taste
is excellent.
- How much is it?
- $480.
I'll try the yellow one on again.
You have rescued me.
Merci beaucoup.
- I'm glad I could help.
- The first day you came here,
to myself I say,
"This is a lady
of taste and judgment."
You told me I smelled.
Pardon?
- You said I needed to bathe more often.
- No.
I was as useless
as the Polish girl.
- Until now.
- No no.
My English...
still sometimes I misspeak.
I am grateful, Marguerite,
very grateful.
For your little one.
Ivory...
For her beautiful hair.
My daughter didn't help you,
madame Jeunet.
I did.
I just had to try it on.
It is beautiful, isn't it?
Ah!
Smell that air, the salt?
I'd like to live
by the ocean someday.
I have a cousin, a rich kid...
Ok, the rich kid took the grand
tour, sailed all over world,
but he puked the entire way.
Seasickness.
I gotta piss.
You need to go?
I'll stretch my legs.
Shouldn't have done that.
- Done what?
- Tried to plunge for my weapon.
What are you talking about?
You plunged at me,
tried to commandeer my gun
That's why I killed you.
I spoke to
my friend, the art dealer.
He's not interested,
unfortunately.
But you seemed so optimistic.
Well, he's staying in Europe.
Did he say why?
His response was in a wire.
Surely with your husband home
your financial burden
has eased.
- You'll have other chances.
- When?
I'll make some inquiries,
but honestly...
Your style is a rather cheap
imitation of Mary Cassatt's.
I was in the
woods with my boyfriend Ernie.
He said to me,
"It's dark out here.
I wish had a lantern."
I said, "Me too.
You've been munching on the
grass for the past 10 minutes!"
"Speaking of that," he said,
"how come you never tell me
when you reach a climax?"
"Well, Ernie," I said,
"it's because you're never
around when it happens."
There's nothing wrong
with being an opportunist.
In fact, it's a trait I admire.
The steel pier, the boulevard project...
You were Johnny-on-the-spot with those.
A good Christian, family man,
- well-liked in the community.
- Very impressive.
- What are you looking for?
- The other shoe.
Right now I'd like to sing
a little number for you
called "Some of these Days."
Perhaps Mrs. Bader
would like a better view.
Have I told you how beautiful
you look in that dress?
It was a gift
from Madame Jeunet.
♪ Some of these days ♪
♪ you'll miss me, honey ♪
♪ some of these days ♪
♪ you're gonna be
so lonely ♪
♪ you'll miss my hugging ♪
♪ you're gonna miss
my kissing ♪
♪ you're gonna miss me, honey ♪
♪ when I'm far away... ♪
So I'm assuming
you didn't ask me here
to sing my praises.
Of course not, Edward.
I can't sing a note.
How'd you like to be Mayor?
With you as boss?
I'd have more authority
as street-sweeper.
But a lot more time to run
your construction business.
It's time for a change, Ed,
and you're a solid republican.
- What about Bacharach?
- Mayor Bacharach is ill.
- He will not be seeking re-election.
- What's wrong with him?
I'll make my diagnosis as
soon as I have your answer.
- I have to discuss it with Kathryn.
- Be decisive, Ed.
Roads, hospitals,
convention center...
We can build
great things together.
Of course we'll have to add a
ball field onto that list.
1920.
The world belongs to the young.
We'll let them think it does.
Mayor Edward Bader.
You roll that around
on your tongue.
I'll be in touch.
♪ You've always
had your way ♪
♪ and when you leave me ♪
♪ you know it's gonna
grieve me ♪
♪ gonna miss
your big fat mama ♪
♪ your mama,
some of these days. ♪
Stand back, ladies and gentlemen,
- or face the wrath of Mombo...
- Hah!
...Tribal chieftain of the Zulu...
from the dark continent of Africa!
Raised among lions
and every bias fierce,
the Zulu have a thirst
for human blood!
Pity the poor souls
unfortunate enough
to spend the last
of their days...
We'll need to stop by
the ambassador.
I told Jim Neary we meet
him for a nightcap.
It's rather late, isn't it?
- Hiya, Nuck.
- Evening.
Nucky?
Nucky Thompson!
Nein.
You filthy bastard!
Come here!
Stop stop!
Is that a cop?
Get a cop!
He went that way!
Call an ambulance!
Oh my God!
Missus, are you all right?
- Help!
- Is she dead?
♪ you're gonna be
so lonely ♪
♪ you'll miss
my hugging ♪
♪ you're gonna miss
my kissing ♪
♪ you're gonna
miss me, honey ♪
♪ when I'm far away ♪
♪ I feel so lonely ♪
♪ for you only ♪
♪ 'cause you know,
honey ♪
♪ you've always
had your way ♪
♪ and when
you leave me ♪
♪ you know it's gonna
grieve me ♪
♪ gonna miss
your big fat mama ♪
♪ your mama,
some of these days. ♪
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.podnapisi.net