What do you want from him?
I don't want to lose this.
- Do you love him?
- I'm fond of him.
Why won't you return my calls?
What does she have
that I don't have?
- She's a shop girl.
- We'll talk about it later.
How many times you think
you can knock over
Nucky Thompson's bagman
before he bites back?
You been to Lolly Steinman's?
End of a Saturday they got
150 grand in the cage.
May I present
Senator Walter Edge
and the honorable Frank Hague,
Mayor of Jersey City.
I want the highway.
You're putting a big bet
on Walter Edge.
I wouldn't. He's a silent
partner in a paving company.
- Where?
- Jersey City, where your roads aren't.
Nucky Thompson didn't get
where he is by being naive.
He could stop giving me money.
What about Jimmy?
I would have thought
he'd send something...
if not for me, for Tommy.
He's a genius, this kid.
They'd come
after us eventually.
Us? So you're
sticking around.
I could use a dozen like you.
The World Series was
months ago, lawyer Fallon.
And the horse shit
hasn't dried yet.
Do you have children
of your own, Mr. Thompson?
I do not.
Go home, Nelson.
Visit your wife.
That's an order.
The whole thing's
a game, isn't it?
So easy for you.
Well, I'll keep at it.
Maybe one day
I'll lie as good as you.
It's lie as well as me,
you dolt.
Want to be taken seriously?
Then learn how to speak.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Well, who was it?
Fella got off on the wrong floor.
He was drunk.
The General Motors Convention.
That's it?
There's nobody else out there?
That waiting room's packed
when Nucky's in town.
I don't get it. It's not like
the city's closed for business.
When he's away, I'm in charge.
What's so complicated?
People are funny...
creatures of habit.
They need a favor, they know
Nucky's the man to see.
Get me some coffee.
You don't think
I can do what he does?
The glad-handing,
the backslapping?
I'll buy a nickel joke book
down at the five and dime,
I'll be the toast
of the town myself.
- Oh.
- Oh what?
I forgot!
Nuck's in Chicago.
And I'm here,
so what do you want?
This Friday
my daughter's being
fitted for her leg braces.
I-I was hoping
to take the day,
have someone else
make my collections.
- Who usually fills in?
- Neary,
but with the indictment,
I got his route now too.
Your kid has polio?
Take the day off.
Be with your girl.
Are you sure?
I just said it, didn't I?
Why would I not be sure?
Thanks.
- Good day, sir.
- Here you go.
Thank you, sir.
My wire specifically requested
the presidential suite.
I'm sorry, sir.
General Wood has also made that request.
- He's jumping the gun a bit, isn't he?
- Sir?
General Wood is only
a candidate for president.
Oh yes, of course.
The ambassador suite is
quite lovely as well, sir.
Fine, then give Wood
the ambassador
- and bring my bags up to the presidential suite.
- Sir, I...
Let me tell you the difference
between me and General Wood.
He is a war hero,
former Army Chief of Staff
and practically a shoo-in for the
Republican presidential nomination.
I, on the other hand,
am a magnificent tipper.
I'd like a bucket of ice
and three bottles
of Canadian club
waiting in the parlor.
Please make yourself comfortable
while we prepare the suite.
All this empty space, I wonder
where they hide the hootch.
Well, if it isn't
Marley's ghost.
Senator Edge, whatever
brings you to Chicago?
Oh, I don't know.
I heard the Republicans were
throwing a little shindig,
- thought I'd drop by.
- Grab the V.P. nod while you're here?
I hadn't actually
considered that,
but now that you mention it...
- How are you, Nuck?
- Well, I can't complain,
but that doesn't mean I won't.
I'm wondering if you'd
do me a favor.
Harry Daugherty's hosting a reception
tonight, he asked me to drop by.
Warren Harding's
campaign manager?
- Who cares about Harding?
- Well, nobody,
but Daugherty's
a good man to know.
If you'd go on my behalf?
I have a pressing engagement.
Well, don't press on her
too hard, Walter.
You know me well, my friend.
I do indeed.
We're gonna take
this thing, Nucky.
And as soon as we do,
the sky's the limit.
The sky?
I'm only interested
in the roads,
Mr. Vice President.
- So you'll see Daugherty?
- You know me... I'll see 'em all.
You're a real pal, Nuck.
- Gentlemen.
- Ah!
The Senator seems
in a good humor.
Go check on the room.
- Peridot.
- Is that what it's called?
Not emeralds, but not nothing.
Do you think he
picked it himself?
I don't know.
Either he's got better taste in women's
jewelry than a red-blooded man should,
- or someone's doing his shopping for him.
- Mr. Kessler, perhaps.
- The little bochey fellow?
- Mm-hmm.
What's he got hidden
under his woolens?
The kaiser's mustache.
You are a terrible influence.
How is your Harry?
My Harry's fine.
How's yours?
We should
get some more cream cakes.
Oh, why not? We can bring
them back for the children.
- Not so bad sometimes, is it?
- What?
The whole ball of wax.
- Margaret.
- Madame Jeunet.
Oh, you must assist me.
- In what?
- Where'd you go?!
Ahhh.
Everybody knows
everybody, isn't that swell?
- How's tricks, Lucy?
- Don't act like you care.
She wishes to make a large
purchase, but her credit...
Mr. Thompson has made clear
that he no longer...
What are you two
whispering about?
Americans don't whisper.
I have asked Margaret
to help me to explain...
Oh, she'll help.
She's very helpful.
Aren't you,
Mrs. MacDougal?
- Schroeder.
- Is that Irish for "bitch"?
You're not at your best now
and you should leave.
Oh, you're in charge
of the lobby now too?
- Lucy.
- My old friend Annabelle.
You wouldn't steer
me wrong, would you?
- No, I wouldn't.
- You're about as phony as that wig.
Miss Danziger,
you must stop now.
You think that
he's your friend?
You think you understand him?
And what if I did?
Then you're the dumbest Dora
I ever met.
The next time won't be
nearly as pleasant.
What do you think?
She looks pretty.
The grocery bill...
it's overdue.
- How much is it?
- Nearly $11, dear.
Hello, Tommy.
Did you check the box?
I saw the postman as well.
There was nothing else.
Perhaps it's time
you get a job.
My friend Mary
said the same thing.
Have you considered
selling Little Dot?
- I'm not sure what that is.
- It's a perfume company.
The ladies who go door to door?
Some of their fragrances
are really quite lovely.
The Violet, Lily of the Valley.
I don't think it's for me.
That's right,
you bohemian types
go au naturel.
I've worn perfume.
I was talking about the job.
There's an art dealer
in New York...
Greenwich Village...
and he's agreed
to look at my work
with an eye
toward selling it.
- Oh really?
- There are no guarantees, of course.
- But Mary...
- Your friend.
Yes.
She thinks I have
a good chance.
You could take a stenography
course as well, you know.
- Sir?
- Yes?
We got another one.
I haven't confirmed it yet,
but word on the street
is the D.A.
is sniffing around
some of the White Sox.
Then he'd be wise to put
a clothespin on his nose.
Any idea which players?
Cicotte and Jackson,
near as I can tell.
Get the farm boys to spill
their milk, is that the idea?
Fallon & McGee.
How may I help you?
It doesn't matter what they
say if Attell won't talk.
Will he?
He's already been
flapping his gums.
And if the D.A.
pulls him in?
He may be able to take a punch,
but put him in a witness chair and
Abe Attell will fold like hot laundry.
Give it to me again.
"Baseball is the heart of America.
As a patriot,
I would never do anything
- to degrade our..."
- Besmirch.
It's better.
"... To 'besmirch'
our national pastime.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this entire ugly affair
began when Abe Attell
and some other cheap gamblers
approached me to fix
the World Series,
a sordid scheme which
every newsboy on Broadway
knows I turned down flat.
And not only was I
not in on the deal,
I furthermore did not bet
one red cent on the Series
after I found out
what was underway."
Isn't it true, sir, that a man named
Sport Sullivan approached you as well?
"I'm approached
by people every day
with all manner
of harebrained schemes.
Certainly suffering fools
can't be illegal."
You know it's not too late
to go to law school, Arnold.
I prefer to make
my living honestly.
- Never get close to a majority.
- Absolutely.
And with Coolidge on the
ticket, I think he has...
- Sir?
- Nucky Thompson.
I'm looking
for Harry Daugherty.
Right over there.
Mr. Thompson.
Harry Daugherty.
- Call me Nucky.
- Nucky it is.
- What can I get you?
- I wouldn't say no to a bourbon.
Two double
bourbons on the double.
Say that 10 times fast.
Senator Edge sends his regrets.
Well, he'll certainly
be missed,
but those in the know say
you're the man to see.
I suppose that depends
on what you want.
"As Nucky Thompson goes,
so goes the New Jersey delegation."
Well, is it true?
We'll have to wait
and see, now won't we?
That's why
I wanted to meet you.
See, I think Warren Harding
could go all the way.
Put Edge on that ticket
and we've got a winner.
I like a long shot as much
as the next fella, Harry,
but I'm not quite sure
how you're doping that out.
The front runner's are
Wood and Lowden, right?
That Senate inquiry is
a black mark on 'em both.
- The campaign finance.
- Then there's Johnson,
who started the damn
investigation to begin with,
which didn't exactly
win him any friends.
The field has no first-raters and
Harding's the best of the second-raters.
Not exactly a rousing endorsement,
but it happens to be true.
He certainly
looks like a president.
That's half the battle,
my friend.
More than half if those
trollops get the vote.
- Great meal last night, Harry.
- Do the right thing, boys,
- and steak won't be the only thing on the menu.
- You bet, Harry.
I have quite an appetite
myself, you know?
You should meet Warren.
You're gonna like him.
Mr. Smith... he invited me.
- My name should be on the list.
- Miss Britton, go to your room.
- I'll make sure he knows...
- Jess, would you please just
tell Warren that I'm here.
Senator and Mrs. Harding, I'd
like you to meet Nucky Thompson,
an esteemed member of
the New Jersey delegation.
- How do you do?
- An honor and a privilege.
Senator, I read a speech
you gave back in May
in Rhode island, I believe.
- "Back to normal."
- Boston, at the Home Market Club.
- Right.
- It was quite something.
- Very well done.
- That's nothing.
I can spend hours bloviating.
You see, Americans don't want
someone looking
to stir things up.
They want stability,
someone dedicated
to safeguarding
America first...
...To prosper America
first, to think of America first.
My best judgment for
what America needs now
is to steady down, to get
squarely on our feet...
Warren, there's a few other
gentlemen I'd like you to meet.
Nucky, I hope you'll
consider what we discussed.
A pleasure.
You must be awfully
proud of your husband.
It's a terrible wretched thing.
A fortune-teller told me
he'll die in office.
Thank you, Miss Britton.
- Evening.
- Good evening.
- Beautiful child.
- Oh, thank you.
A young Republican,
I'm guessing.
She certainly is.
- And what brings you to the Convention?
- Oh...
We're, um, friends
of Mr. Harding's.
Well, it's good to have
friends in politics.
Do you have children yourself?
No.
I had a son.
He died.
I'm sorry.
Bless this food, o lord,
and ourselves
to thy loving service;
That we may always
continue in thy faith
and fear to the honor
and glory of thy name,
through Jesus Christ our lord.
- Amen.
The garden...
The tulips are looking
a little ragged.
What's wrong?
You put yourself
through this every month.
It means I'm not fully a woman.
- Yes, you are, very much so.
- No.
No. No baby
will grow inside me.
And in the place of that joy,
every 28 days the blood flows
and then I can't help it,
so do the tears.
Please eat.
I, uh, ran into Naomi
Ellsworth at the milliner.
Mmm.
She said I might be able
to get some help.
Must everyone know
our private affairs?
She had difficulty
conceiving herself.
There was a... a blockage
in her tubes as well.
Why must we always
go on about this?
If the lord wanted us...
If the lord wanted us
to die of appendicitis
then he wouldn't have given
us the ability to treat it.
That's Naomi Ellsworth talking.
I want to get this fixed.
There's a physician in Manhattan.
- He can perform a surgery.
- Surgery?!
It's $270.
My salary barely meets
expenses as it is.
I want to give you
a son, Nelson.
All I want is for you
to be happy, Rose.
I'll do what I can.
Now please, dear, eat.
- She knows what she wants!
- Cover your eyes.
You're too good.
- Get in there!
- Here we go.
- Look at that.
- I'll tell you,
if they had nuns like that, I might
have made it past sixth grade.
I don't think anything could have
got you past the sixth grade, Jim.
What's this now?
- Oh boy.
- It's called a snatch, Al.
What's that smell like
on a hot summer day?
Jesus, where do they
get these women?
If I find out, I'm sure as
hell keeping it to myself.
- Ah. Sorry, boys.
- God damn it.
- Come on!
- It was just getting good.
- There we go.
- Back in business.
- All right!
- So are we all straight on the collections?
Yeah, I'll take the inlet
to Maryland Avenue,
Fleming will take
the other side.
♪ I'll be in Scotland
before ye! ♪
How about the casino?
- I'll take that myself.
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
June and I have an affair...
her cousin's wedding.
I'll swing by on the way home.
Sister Mary Catherine!
- Uh-oh, bad girl!
- Oh yeah.
Fellas, I think I'm
joining the priesthood.
Come on, what's
going on back there, Boyd?
Oh!
- Jesus Christ!
- What the...
- Boyd, nice work.
- To too hot to watch.
Good job, Boyd!
- Oh shit.
- Good thinking.
Ho, what you doing?
These are friends of mine.
Convenient you waited
till he was done.
Standard operating procedure.
It's a new world.
If he could talk, I'm sure
Charlie Sheridan would agree.
You read about that, huh?
Your boy Jimmy? My boy.
Two rums, Tommy! Oh...
wait, that's right...
we ain't got any.
You just can't make
your point, huh?
Well, where the fuck
is it already?
McCoy's sailing up
from Bimini as we speak.
On a raft?
I need delivery.
These broads are over the moon with
this Mary Pickford cocktail.
They mix the rum
with grenadine.
'Cause the bootleg stuff
tastes like shit.
So you're making a show
at the Convention, eh?
It's so nice
to meet your acquaintance.
I'm a politician.
There are some things
you can't buy in a cathouse.
Salut.
So let me ask you, any scuttlebutt
on this Harry Daugherty?
- Never heard of him.
- He's Warren Harding's campaign manager.
- Never heard of him neither.
- He's a Senator from Ohio.
- He's running for president.
- Why didn't you say so?
Ohio? You should
talk to Judge Graves.
- Who's he?
- See? You don't know everybody.
Your Honor!
I want to introduce you
to a dear friend of mine...
Nucky Thompson
from Atlantic City.
- How do you do?
- Oh, I've never been to Jersey.
Staten Island once,
but that was years ago.
Well, you're welcome any time.
At my expense, of course.
- Much obliged.
- Here.
So I hear you have some
insight into Warren Harding.
Harding? He's a puppet for the
fast-money boys in Cleveland.
I used to sit
on the bench there.
- You like his chances?
- I like them better with
Harry Daugherty behind him.
- A little cagey, that one.
- But he knows how to treat a friend,
I can tell you that
from experience.
These Ohio fellas know what
they're doing, Mr. Thompson.
Five presidents
since the civil war.
Judge Graves?
Belle's arrived.
Gentlemen.
I never keep a lady waiting.
- A pleasure.
- Enjoy.
Loves his dark meat, this one.
Gotta bring her in special
from the black belt.
Go, get out of here, go!
- You think it's funny? Tough guy, move it.
- I gotta take my money.
- Move it! Piece of shit.
- Let go of me.
The lady says stop,
that's what it means.
If I see you here again, I'll
cut your fucking pecker off.
- Get him outta here.
- Move it.
Nucky.
James.
- Is everything all right?
- Why wouldn't it be?
What are you doing here?
I've been coming to Chicago
since before you were born.
Who do you think lit that fire?
You're looking well.
New suit.
Mr. Torrio's been
very helpful.
Call us a cab, Eddie.
Excuse me.
If you want, I could
give you fellas a lift.
Old times, eh?
Sure, why not?
Somehow, James, we've all been
managing to get along without you.
Your family as well.
- How are they?
- Why don't you call and find out?
I write her every week, Nuck.
She never writes me back.
Next time you buy
a new wristwatch for yourself?
Don't.
Send them the money instead.
Lolly?
Hello!
What the hell are you doing?
The fuck's going on here?
Don't fucking move!
Get the bag!
You follow us,
we'll kill youse all!
I'll tell you, as much as they
crow about their meat here,
for my money it's
the occidental in D.C.
Your money? When's the last
time you paid for a dinner?
Mmm, right after
McKinley was elected.
How bad?
- Excuse me, Walter.
- Everything okay?
I need a telephone.
- Hello?
- It's me.
What time is it?
I don't know, late.
Are you all right?
No. Margaret,
there's been an incident.
My brother's been shot.
Oh my God, is he dead?
No, I don't think so.
- I need you to do something for me.
- I'll go to him immediately.
Uh, but I'll need
to call a sitter.
No. Actually,
it's my office.
Yes?
Eli's being cared for.
He's home with his family.
There's a doctor.
I need you to go to the Ritz.
- Very well.
- My office... it's been left unattended.
I'll need you to safeguard
a few things,
some business records.
What about Mr. Fleming
or one of your aldermen?
I don't know what's
happening right now
and until I return I prefer
to rely only on you.
Can I do that?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
In the top drawer of my desk
is a ledger book.
I want you to take it out, leave it
closed and bring it to my closet.
In the back, behind the shoe
rack, is a compartment.
Slip it in there and stay in the suite
with your children until I return.
When will that be?
I'm on the first
train home tomorrow.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
What are you drinking?
Whiskey.
I figured only champagne
now with that get-up.
It's bespoke.
Al bought it for me.
Who's your friend?
War buddy.
Richard Harrow.
To the lost.
So I'm assuming
this is not a social call.
I need you to come home, James.
Need or want?
Eli's been shot.
They robbed Lolly's.
- Who did?
- I don't know.
We're at war, kid.
They hit Chalky's
a few months back,
killed one of his men,
robbed O'Neill right out
in the open on the boards.
- And now this?
- Someone's got it in their head
that I'm weak, that I have no
real means of retaliation.
You got the whole Sheriff's
department on your payroll.
And the Sheriff in bed
with a bullet in his gut.
There are things I may require that I'm
uncomfortable asking of Eli anyway,
particularly with
the election coming.
This afternoon when you saw me,
you looked at me like I was
something you scraped off your boot.
Now it's 4:00 in the morning,
the world's closing in,
- I'm your long lost son?
- Don't overestimate yourself, James.
Why shouldn't I, Nuck?
I'm doing very well here.
And how far will that go?
You're Irish, Torrio's Italian.
You'll always be an outsider.
You know this suit
cost 70 bucks?
You're about as subtle as a kick
in the teeth, you know that?
5% of anything
that comes in by boat
and 10% of anything
that comes in on wheels.
And that fed?
What do I do about him?
I'll work that out.
I got to think about it.
You do that,
but whatever you decide,
don't ever keep me
waiting again.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Mrs. Schroeder.
Who is this?
Well.
This is rather clandestine.
Something tells me you're no
stranger to backroom meetings.
Quite a back room.
I need to head home.
Something came up.
Before the Convention
even starts?
I've made inquiries, Harry.
Heard good things about
you from Judge Graves.
You mean you heard I play ball.
Well, don't you?
The babe's got nothing
on Harry Daugherty.
I've thought about
what you said.
It's slim, but Harding
has a chance.
I thought you were backing Wood.
I think he'll
deadlock with Lowden.
- And if that happens, they're both done.
- Delegates won't cross over.
Don't expect Harding to be nominated early,
but come the fifth or sixth ballot?
Those bleary-eyed delegates will want to
nominate somebody who could actually win.
If that happens,
I'm prepared to throw
the Jersey delegation
behind Harding.
In exchange for Edge getting V.P.
In exchange for Edge
not getting V.P.
What am I missing here?
That Walter Edge is a dirty
backstabbing chiseler
who gave my road money
to Frank Hague.
How do you know that?
Because Hague's an even
bigger backstabbing chiseler,
not to mention a friend.
That's rich, boy.
I'll tell ya.
You can tell me something
else while you're at it.
Like how you propose to take
care of Harding's lady trouble.
Which lady?
Which trouble?
- There are more than one?
- Showgirls, shopgirls,
I've lost count,
to tell you the truth.
One of them's even
blackmailing him.
The skirt with the little girl?
Naw, she's okay.
She's in love is all.
- Name's Nan Britton.
- And the baby's his?
It could cost him the election.
Then let me help.
I'll bring her to A.C.,
put her up till November. I've got
a lady-friend with kids of her own,
they'll look in on her. After the
election, she's your problem again.
And then I get my road money.
I'll have to sell it to Warren.
I'm sure you're quite
the salesman.
You know Al Jolson agreed
to write his campaign song.
Eddie Cantor's better.
Love to hear from you.
I'm just surprised, that's all.
What, a fella can't call
his mother once in a while?
You can call me
twice a day if you like.
I saw Nucky.
He was out here for the Convention.
I'm assuming you've heard
what happened to his brother.
Yeah, that was something, huh?
I swear, this world is going
to hell in a handbasket.
Yeah.
You sound lonesome, baby.
I was thinking of you.
Are you eating?
Yeah, of course.
Why don't you come home,
honeypot?
I don't know.
So what can you tell me
about this Luciano fella?
Well...
Where do I begin?
Yeah, those two.
This way, Miss Britton.
Nucky!
I got your message.
Where are you going?
- Home.
- But the delegates haven't voted yet.
Who's gonna get
all our ducks in a row?
- Why don't you ask Frank Hague?
- Hague?
What's this all about?
We've known each other a long time,
Wally, so why don't you cut the crap?
"Wally"?
You're speaking to a
United States Senator.
And that's all you'll ever be.
You made a deal with Hague
to fuck me over.
- Nucky, I have no idea what you're talking about...
- Don't insult me.
It was just politics.
I'll make it up to you later.
Later when?
When I'm in the White House.
Senator, the only chance you
have of entering the White House
is on a guided fucking tour.
"I love your back,
I love your breasts,
daring to feel
where my face rests.
I love your skin
so soft and white,
so dear to feel
and sweet to bite.
I love your knees,
their dimples kiss.
I lo your ways of giving bliss.
I love your poise
of perfect thighs,
the way they hold me
in paradise."
That was the first love
poem Warren ever wrote me.
He's got quite
a way with words.
We'll be making a coal stop
in 30 minutes, folks.
I'm going to freshen up.
- Anything out of Chicago?
- Just came over the wires.
Warren Harding received the
nomination after 10 ballots.
That imbecile
is going to be the next
President of the United States.
"My dearest Rose,
like Sarah, Rebecca
and Hannah before you,
I urge you to trust
in God's plan,
not just for your own sake,
but also the sake
of any offspring
he may see fit
to bestow upon us,
not only so that you may
know him better,
but walk more closely
in his footsteps.
Your devoted husband, Nelson."
Nucky.
Oh my God.
Everything's going to be fine.
It might take awhile,
but we'll get him
back on his feet.
Give us a minute, will you?
How are you doing,
little brother?
They came out of nowhere.
Nothing I could do.
It's only money, forget it.
It's more than money.
We're under siege.
I asked Jimmy to come back.
Jimmy?
We need help, Eli.
How many years
have we been doing this?
Not once has this
ever happened.
It's a new world.
♪ Please don't be offended ♪
♪ I preach to you awhile ♪
♪ tears are
out of place in eyes ♪
♪ that were meant to smile ♪
♪ look for
the silver lining ♪
♪ whene'er a cloud
appears in the blue ♪
♪ remember somewhere ♪
♪ the sun is shining ♪
♪ and so the right thing ♪
♪ to do ♪
♪ is make it shine for you ♪
♪ a heart full of joy
and gladness ♪
♪ will always banish ♪
♪ sadness and strife ♪
♪ so always look for ♪
♪ the silver lining ♪
♪ and try to find ♪
♪ the sunny side of life ♪
♪ look for the silver lining ♪
♪ and try to find ♪
♪ the sunny side of life. ♪
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.podnapisi.net